[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Stanford University,
斯坦福大学,
>> Okay, well welcome to Stanford CS193P Developing
> >好的,欢迎来到斯坦福CS193P发展
Applications for iOS winter of 2017,
iOS应用程序2017年冬天,
This is Lecture number 15 and
这是15和讲座
our only topic today is segues,
今天是我们唯一的话题而已,
This is the segues lecture,
这是segue讲座,
You've learned show segues and show detail segues, which
你学到segue segue并展示细节,
work in navigation controllers and split view controllers and
在导航控制器和视图控制器分裂和工作
now we're gonna learn all the rest of the kinds of segues
现在我们要学习所有其他类型的segue
that you can use to build your application,
,您可以使用它们来构建您的应用程序,
So let's start with mode segue,
让我们开始segue模式,
So now a modal segue is interesting,
现在模态segue很有趣,
One, you, when you segue modally,
一个,你,当你segue语气地,
you take an MVC that you're segueing to,
你把你segue MVC,
And it takes over the entire screen, okay?
接管整个屏幕,好吗?
That's why it's called modal,
这就是为什么它被称为模态,
because you're in a mode [LAUGH] where you can only
因为你在一个你只能模式[笑]
interact with that MVC,
与MVC,
There's no back button,
没有后退按钮,
There's no tab bar to click on,
没有标签栏点击,
There's no way to do anything else in the app except for
没有办法做任何其他的应用程序除外
what that MVC is doing,
MVC是做什么,
Why would you ever want to do this?
为什么你会想要这样做吗?
Well, sometimes you get to a point in your application
嗯,有时候你可以在您的应用程序
where you need some information from your user and
你需要一些信息从你的用户和在哪里
you just can't proceed without it,
你不能没有它,
So, my example here is, let's say I'm in a contacts app,
所以,我的例子是,假设我在联系人应用程序,
like the contacts app on your phone and you get to a point
联系人应用程序在你的手机和一个点
here where you're looking through contacts and
在这里你是通过接触和
you say, "well I want to add a contact",
你说,“我想要添加一个联系人”,
Alright, so you're going to press this little +
好的,那么你要按这个小+
button in upper right hand corner,
按钮在右上角,
When you do that, a whole new MVC,
当你这样做,一个全新的MVC,
the add contact MVC slides up from the button and
添加联系人MVC和幻灯片的按钮
you notice there's no back button there because I'm
你注意到因为我没有后退按钮
not in the navigation pushed and instead of a back button,
不是在导航和推后退按钮,
this one happens to have a cancel button right here,
这一发生在有一个取消按钮,
But there's nothing I can do now with this application,
但是现在没有什么我可以做与这个应用程序,
except for what's on this screen,
除了在这个屏幕上,
So, I could fill out the field to add a contact,
所以,我可以填写字段添加一个联系人,
I could hit cancel or done, that's all I can do,
我可以取消或完成,这就是我能做的,
And it's perfectly fine to have a modal
完美的模态
MVC that brings up another modal MVC,
MVC,带来另一种模态MVC,
In fact, this one does,
事实上,这一个,
I'm adding a new contact here and
我在这里添加一个新的联系人
I'm going to add a photo for my contact,
我要为我的联系人添加照片,
So I'm gonna click this add photo button, right here, and
所以我要点击这个按钮添加照片,,
when I do, another MVC, presumably the camera, or
当我做的,另一个MVC,想必相机,或
the photo library, or
照片库,或
the photo choosing MVC, comes up on top,
照片选择MVC,出现在上面,
And again, I can't do anything now until I've dealt with this
再一次,我现在不能做任何事情直到我处理这个
and, presumably I could take a photo,
大概我可以拍照,
that would be one way to get out of this,
这将是一个办法,
Or I could hit cancel so let's go ahead and hit cancel in
或者我可以点击取消我们点击取消
this one, when we do that we go back to the previous model
这个,当我们做,我们回到前面的模型
one and here if we hit cancel on this one we are going to go
这里如果我们取消这个我们要走了
back to the original one that we had right,
回到最初的我们有,
So it is two order model viewer control is it kinda
这是二阶模型查看器控制它
takes over your app for a little bit now,
接管你的应用一点了,
you gotta think a little bit about modal view controllers,
你要想一下模态视图控制器,
They're so easy to put up,
他们太容易了,
that they can be abused a little bit,
他们可以被滥用,
Users tend to be slightly disconcerted by modal MVCs,
用户倾向于由模态mvc有点不安的,
Because they get comfortable with their app and
因为他们熟悉他们的应用程序
they know where the tabs are,
他们知道标签在哪里,
And they know how to go backwards and
他们知道如何倒退和
forwards in navigation controllers,
前锋在导航控制器,
And then, all of a sudden, all they can do is this one thing,
然后,突然之间,这是所有他们能做的一件事,
Now, sometimes it makes perfect sense,
现在,有时候很有道理,
Like add contacts of course that the user understands I'm
当然像添加联系人,用户理解我
adding a contact that I can click over and
我可以点击添加一个联系人
do something else,
做其他的事情,
Well there are some users who might say why can I
也有一些用户可能会说为什么我可以
click over do some of the things right now?
点击现在在做的一些事情吗?
I need to do that to add these contacts or whatever,
我需要添加这些联系人之类的,
So, I tried to stay away from modal view controllers as much
所以,我试着远离模态视图控制器
as possible but things in navigation controllers and
但是事情在导航控制器和
tab button controllers, and things like that but
选项卡按钮控制器,等等
there are times, when it's absolutely, necessary,
有时,当它绝对必要的,
So how do you set one of these modal segways up?
那么如何设置这些模态赛格威?
Super easy,
超级简单,
You just control-drag,
你只是control - drag,
And when you control-drag, instead of saying show or
当你control - drag,而不是说节目或
detail, you're going to say present modally,
的细节,你会说现在的形式,
Now, normally, as with any segway,
现在,正常情况下,对于任何赛格威,
you're going to be segwaying from like a bar button item or
你要从栏按钮项目或赛格威
just a regular button, or a row in a tableview, but if for
只是一个普通的按钮,或表视图中的一行,但是如果
some reason you want to put something up module
某些原因你想提出一些模块
from something else basically from code,
从别的基本代码,
You don't forget about this method that actually
你不要忘记这个方法
in a previous lecture called perform segue with identify,
在之前的讲座叫做执行segue与识别,
we're talk about,
我们谈谈,
You can set up a segue in your story board by just control
你可以设置一个segue故事板的控制
dragging from the little view controller icon at
小视图控制器图标拖动
the top of your scene that little yellow thing,
你的场景,黄色的东西,
it's at the very top part of any scene in your story board,
它的顶端的一部分在你的故事板,
In control drag from that, to any other MVC,
从,控制拖动到其他MVC,
set it to be present modal, and then inspect that segue,
设置当前模态,然后继续检查,
Give it an identifier, and
给它一个标识符
then call this method in your code,
然后在代码中调用这个方法,
It will cause that segue to happen, and
它会导致这种情况继续发生,
that MVC will appear modally,
MVC将出现模态,
Also, if you happen to have a view controller in your
还有,如果你碰巧有一个视图控制器
hand like you have a local variable or
就像你有一个局部变量或
something that has a view controller in it,
有一个视图控制器,
which by the way when would that ever happen?
顺便说一下,会在什么时候发生?
Have we seen that happen?
我们看到,发生吗?
I don't think we have yet,
我不认为我们有,
But there are various iOS API that will give you back
但是有各种iOS API将回给你
a view controller,
一个视图控制器,
Like on Wednesday we're gonna talk about alerts and
周三我们要谈论警报和
action sheets,
动作表,
They will give you an MVC which is basically an alert
他们会给你一个MVC基本上是一个警告
that you're gonna put up on the screen,
你要贴在屏幕上,
Also if you want to take a picture with the camera,
如果你想用相机拍照,
you're gonna get this UI image picker controller which is
你会得到这个UI选择控制器的形象
an MVC and you're gonna put it up,
MVC你会放上去的,
And the way you put that up, okay,
你把,,好吧,
anytime you have an MVC in your hand, in a VAR,
在你的手,当你有一个MVC VAR,
Not in the storyboard but in it might be something you
不是在故事板中而是在它可能是你
created out of the storyboard but it's in your in a bar,
创建故事板的但是它是在你的酒吧里,
You just do present,
你只做礼物,
So these are both new controller methods up
这些都是新的控制器方法
here these yellow things,
这些黄色的东西,
And present just takes the view controller you want to
和现在需要你想要的视图控制器
present, whether you wanna animate
现在,你是否想要动画
it appearing on screen which you usually do,
它出现在屏幕上,你通常做什么,
A and then a completion handler,
然后完成处理器,
When animations done it'll call a completion handler,
当动画完成它会打电话给一个完成处理程序,
Often we just ignore that,
我们常常忽略,
That's why it defaults to nil there, okay,
这就是为什么它默认为零,好吧,
Now, when you are causing this modal thing
现在,当你让这个模态的东西
to appear, when it appears,
出现,当它出现时,
it can actually appear in different forms,
它可以出现在不同的形式,
One way is, it can cover the entire screen,
一种方法是,它可以覆盖整个屏幕,
which you're going to always see in
你会一直看到
train trade collections where it tours on like compact,
火车贸易集合,参观像紧凑,
Okay, so that's like iPhone, all right,
好了,这就像iPhone,好吧,
or master maybe of my pad,
或者也许我垫的大师,
In a horizontally compact environment it's going
水平在一个紧凑的环境的
to kind of cover drop the whole space,
覆盖掉整个空间,
But in other places you might want it to appear
但在其他地方你可能希望它出现
as a Popover, okay?
作为一个弹出窗口,好吗?
Or you might even want it to appear as kind of a form
或者你甚至可能想要作为一种形式出现
sheet, a smaller than the huge iPad screen,
表,比巨大的iPad屏幕小,
So when you setup your segue, you can go and inspect it and
所以当你设置你的继续,你可以去检查它
you can set how you want it to appear, okay?
你可以设置你想要如何出现,好吗?
And you can just take a look of those prime out, page and
你可以看看这些',和页面
form sheet and see what they look like, and see which one,
格式表,看看他们是什么样子,看看哪一个,
that's what it's gonna look like when it, it gets there,
这就是它会看起来像的时候,就在那里,
You like there, so
你喜欢那里,所以
In horizontally compact environments, okay,
在横向紧凑的环境中,好的,
they aren't really narrow environments,
他们不是真的狭窄的环境中,
it's always by default going to adapt to full screen,
它总是在默认情况下会适应全屏,
no matter what, you put in there, but I'm gonna show you,
无论如何,你放在那里,但是我要告诉你,
hopefully, if we have time in the demo, how you can override
希望,如果我们有时间在演示中,你如何可以覆盖
that adapting that behavior, that automatic adapting
适应这一行为,自动调整
behavior preparing for a modal segue, it's
行为准备模态segue,
exactly the same as any other segue you've ever seen, right?
一模一样其它segue你见过,对吧?
You just check the identifier, see if the destination does
你只是检查标识符,看看目的地
the thing you're looking for, and then prepare it,
你要找的东西,然后准备它,
What about hearing back from a Modal MVC?
听到从模态MVC呢?
So you put a Modal MVC up like that contacts thing and it
所以你把模态MVC,这样接触的事情
collects all the information for the new contact,
收集新联系人的所有信息,
How do you communicate back?
你怎么沟通?
Here's the new contact, okay?
这是新的联系,好吗?
So, there's a couple of things there,
所以,这里有几件事情,
One, you know, that new contact thing might just be
一个,你知道,这可能是新接触的事情
creating that contact in a database,
在数据库中创建,接触,
And, and you don't need to do anything,
,你不需要做任何事情,
You just dismiss the modal view controller,
你只是把模态视图控制器,
When it comes back, the other view controller is looking in
当它回来时,在其他视图控制器
the same database, and it sees it appear,
相同的数据库,它看到它出现,
It's probably using a fetch results controller or
它可能使用一个控制器或获取结果
something like that, and it sees it as it appears and
这样,它看来似乎和
magically just works, but sometimes you might be
神奇的作品,但有时你可能会
creating something where you do need to
创造一些你需要的地方
communicate back and you're gonna use an unwind segway for
交流回来,你要使用一个放松赛格威
that, and I'm gonna talk about unwind in a few slides here,
,我要讲放松几张幻灯片,
But that's how you're going to communicate back from a modal
但这是如何从模态进行通信
view controller,
视图控制器,
How do you get the modal view controller
你怎么得到模态视图控制器
to go way like when you hit the cancel button?
去像当你点击取消按钮?
The answer is that the presenting view controller
答案是呈现视图控制器
the view controller that puts it up okay the things you said
所说的视图控制器好了你说的事情
way from that thing is responsible for dismissing it,
从那件事负责解散,
And it does it with these methods dismiss animated,
与这些方法把动画,它
okay and that when you say dismiss to NBC it means
好吧,当你说把NBC它的意思
Dismiss any view controller I've put up,
把我提出的任何视图控制器,
That's what this means, okay?
这意味着什么,好吗?
Dismiss ones I've put up,
驳回的我了,
And, the good news is, okay, a lot of times you'd wanna do
好消息是,你想要做的好,很多时候
this in the cancel button of a thing that was presented, but
这个取消按钮的东西了,但是
of course, you can't send this to yourself,
当然,你不能把这自己,
But luckily, every view controller knows
但幸运的是,每一个视图控制器都知道
who presented it,
谁提出了它,
So, it can just get its presenting view controller,
所以,它就能展示视图控制器,
There's a, bar called presenting view controller,
有一个酒吧叫呈现视图控制器,
and it can send dismiss to its presenting view controller,
它可以发送撤销其呈现视图控制器,
You'll see that in the demo as well,
你会发现在演示中,
Online segues by the way, which again I'm going to talk
在线segue顺便说一下,再次我要说话
about in a minute, they automatically dismiss,
大约在一分钟内,他们自动解散,
So, you do not have to call dismiss if you unwind,
所以,你没有打电话给解雇如果你放松,
To communicate information back,
沟通信息,
Now, not only can you control what the modal view control
现在,不仅可以控制模态视图控制
is going to look like when it's up,
像上面的时候,
whether it's full screen or whatever, but
无论是全屏之类的,但是
you can also control how it animates to come up,
您还可以控制如何模拟来的,
And it's the same thing we saw with the other one, you can
和它是一样的我们看到另一个,你可以
flip to have it appear, it can cross this all in there,
翻转已经出现,它可以跨越这一切,
you can slide up from the bottom that's coverVertical is
你可以从底部滑上来就是coverVertical
the default, and you can even partialCurl,
默认的,你甚至可以partialCurl
it will kind of lift it up like a piece of paper and
它将提升它像一张纸
see the new one in behind,
看到新的一个在后面,
In all cases though, no matter how animates on,
在所有情况下,无论多么的,
no matter how are chose, it's modal only that new MVC can be
无论如何选择,新的MVC的模态
interactive with, okay, the other MVC is like the one I
互动与其他MVC是喜欢我
presented it, are kind temporarily disable,
提出,是暂时禁用,
All right, let's talk about that unwind segue,
好吧,让我们来谈谈unwind,
This unwinding,
这种解除,
is the only segue in iOS that does not create a new MVC,
是唯一segue iOS中这并不创建一个新的MVC,
Okay?
好吧?
Show segue, new MVC,
显示segue,新的MVC,
Popover, new MVC,
弹出窗口,新MVC,
But unwind, does not, because in unwind,
但不放松,因为在放松,
you're segueing back to some MVC that already exist,
你segue回一些已经存在的MVC,
That has presented you,
介绍了你,
Okay?
好吧?
Now, what's it good for this unwind, is it's good for
现在,这有利于放松,是很好
communicating back from a modal,
沟通从模态,
It's also good if you have a navigation controller with
还好如果你有一个导航控制器
a whole bunch of things on the stack, and
很多事情在堆栈上,
you want to jump back more than one,
你想跳回不止一个,
You want to do more than one back button's worth, you can
你想做一个以上的后退按钮,你可以
jump back three levels, you can unwind back up your stack,
返回三个级别,您可以放松备份堆栈,
because, though, when you have a navigation controller,
不过,因为当你有一个导航控制器,
all the MVCs, higher on the stack are considered to have
mvc,在堆栈上被认为有较高
presented you by pushing you on the stack, okay?
你推到栈上,好吗?
Which they did, they segued to you with a show, or whatever,
他们做了,他们马上决定显示,等等,
So, that's what unwind is mostly good for,
所以,放松是好的,
How does it work?
它是如何工作的呢?
Well, you don't control drag from the button, or
好吧,你不能控制拖动按钮,或
whatever you want to do the unwind, to the MVC you want,
无论你想做什么放松,MVC你想要的,
Instead, you're gonna Ctrl+drag
相反,你要按Ctrl +阻力
to this little orange button at the top,
这个小橙色按钮在顶部,
You've probably seen this button and
你可能看到过这个按钮
said, mm, what is that thing?
说,嗯,那是什么东西?
It has a tooltip that says Exit, and, indeed,
它有一个工具提示说出口,的确,
that's what you do,
这是你做什么,
When you Ctrl+drag to this thing,
当你Ctrl +拖动到这个东西,
you're creating a segue that is going to exit this MVC,
你创建一个segue会退出这个MVC,
Okay,
好吧,
Now, how do you decide where you are going to go when
现在,你怎么决定你要去的地方
you exit,
你退出,
Well, you are going to do that,
好吧,你要做的,
because you create a special method in another MVC,
因为你在另一个MVC创建一个特殊的方法,
And whenever you create this special method in any MVC
当你创建这种特殊的方法在任何MVC
it gets added to a list inside of X code, and, so
它被添加到列表的内部X代码,因此
when you control drag to exit that list is going to appear,
当你控制拖退出列表会出现,
And you can see I only have
你可以看到我只有
one of them here called go back,
其中一个叫回去,
Now, I'm Ctrl+dragging from a table view raw, so I've got
现在,我Ctrl +拖动从原始表视图,所以我有
the accessory one, and the main table view raw one there,
配件,主要表视图生一个,
But go back, there's the only one,
但回去,还有唯一的一个,
So, when I choose this go back, I'm basically saying,
所以,当我选择回去,我基本上说,
that I wanna segue to some MVC that presented me,
我想一些MVC segue送给我,
it implements the go back method, okay?
它实现了回去的方法,好吗?
That's how unwind work,
这是放松的工作,
Now, let's look at kinda how the code behind all
现在,让我们来看看背后的代码有点多
this works,
其工作原理,
So, in the presenter, the one you're gonna unwind to,
所以,主持人,你要放松,
you have to create a method,
你必须创建一个方法,
And this method has to have two important things,
这个方法有两个重要的事情,
One, it has to be marked @IBAction,
一,必须标明@IBAction,
And two it argument and it can only have one argument,
和两个参数,它只能有一个参数,
it must have one argument, and
它必须有一个参数,
that argument must be of type UI storyboard segue,
这个论点必须类型的UI故事板segue,
because you're going to be segueing to this thing,
因为你要segue这个东西,
Okay, so that's in the view controller you're going
好了,这是在视图控制器你
to unwind to, that you're segueing to,
放松,你segue
So, the code for this kinda looks like this, and
所以,这个有点像这样的代码,
to prepare,
准备,
Of the presenter, so the presented I mean,
的主持人,所以我的意思是,
The prepare,
的准备,
of the thing that's going to be doing the unwind,
要做的事情的放松,
because it's going to be segueing, it gets to prepare,
因为它是segue,准备,
So, it has normal prepare, you can check its identifier,
所以,正常的准备,你可以检查它的标识符,
And when you're in prepare,
当你在准备,
the segue's destination it's gonna be the presenter,
segue的目的地会主持人,
the view controller you're gonna unwind to,
视图控制器你要放松,
So, this code goes in the presented view controller,
所以,这段代码在视图控制器,
the modal view controller, whatever,
模态视图控制器,无论如何,
that you're gonna unwind from,
你要放松,
Then back in the presenter you have code that looks like
然后在主持人你代码的样子
this, the special method with the at sign app, action,
这一点,在标志的特殊方法应用,行动,
ID action and the UI storyboard segue,
故事板和UI segue ID行动,
And inside there, very interestingly,
里面,非常有趣的是,
you're gonna look at the segue's source you know that
你要看看你知道segue的来源
were used to looking a segue destination that's the view
被用来寻找一个segue目的地的看法
controller we are segueing to,
控制器我们segue,
Segue source is the source of the segue, so
Segue源Segue的来源,所以
that's the MVC we're segueing from, so in
MVC我们segue从,所以
an unwind situation for in the go back method, this go back
的解除情况回去的方法,这回去
method, just go back method goes inside the presenter
法,就回去方法走进主持人
right there,
在这里,
The source of the segue is the modal one,
segue的来源是模态的,
And when you do unwind,
当你放松,
you will automatically get dismissed,
你会自动得到了,
See how I disappeared there,
看到我消失了,
I'll get dismissed, and
我会抛弃,和
the presenter will have this go back special method called,
主持人将这回去特殊方法调用时,
So, this, this is how unwind plays out,
所以,这,这就是放松,
okay?
好吧?
It's all about that special method and the presenter,
这是关于特殊方法和主持人,
All right,
好吧,
Another segue is the Popover segue,
另一个segue是弹窗segue,
I'm sure you've all seen this,
我相信你们都看过,
Here's a Popover, this Popover is presenting an MVC,
这是一个弹出窗口,这个弹窗MVC,
which is some kind of search for appointment
这是某种寻找约会吗
MVC there in some calendar app, or something like that,
MVC在一些日历应用程序,或类似的东西,
And, so that's the MVC that's being presented,
,这是MVC的介绍,
Now, when you notice when this is being presented,
现在,当你注意到当这个被提出,
It's in this little white box and there's a little triangle,
在这个小白盒,这里有一个小三角形,
See the little tiny little triangle there?
看到小小三角吗?
It's pointing to the UI element that cause the popover
指向UI元素,导致弹出窗口
to come up,
来,
So, that's usually a bar button item, or button, but
所以,这通常是一个工具栏按钮项,或按钮,但是
you can actually point to any rectangle in any view, okay,
你可以指向任何视图中的任意一个矩形,好吧,
So, for example, if you had an iBooks like app and
所以,例如,如果你有一个iBooks应用等
you have text, and you double click on a word, and
你有文本,你双击一个单词,
you hit define it could bring up a popover with
你可以定义它弹出弹窗
a little arrow is pointing at the word you are defining,
一个小箭头是指向你定义的词,
you see?, so it can point to anything you want there,
你看到了什么?
And notice also that the rest of the UI is kinda grayed out
注意,其余的UI是灰色的
a little bit right the stuff that is not the MVC that is
一些正确的东西不是的MVC
being presented in the popovers kinda grayed out,
被呈现在弹窗有点灰色的,
in fact if you click there you will dismiss the popover, so
事实上如果你点击你会把弹窗,所以
this is also a modal, a popover is also a modal,
这也是一个模态,弹窗也是一个模态,
It only, you can only interact with what's in that popover,
只是,你只能与弹窗,
If you try to click on anything else, it's gonna just
如果你想点击,它会
miss the popover, and end exit the modal state, okay?
小姐弹窗和最终退出模态状态,好吗?
You've probably noticed this from using various iPad apps,
你可能已经注意到从使用各种iPad应用程序,
and by the way, the popover, mostly iPad only, but
顺便说一句,弹出窗口,主要是iPad,但是
not always, you can actually do popovers on the iPhone,
不一定,你可以在iPhone上使用弹窗,
I'll talk a little bit about that as well,
我将谈一谈,
So yeah, popover, just like modal, you control drag,
所以,弹窗,就像模态控制阻力,
you're just gonna set its type to be popover instead of,
你只是要将其类型设置为弹出窗口来代替,
present modal,
现在的模态,
When you're preparing for a popover,
当你准备弹窗,
there's a few extra things you can do, okay,
你可以做一些额外的事情,好吧,
So, all of these presentations,
所以,所有的这些报告,
anytime you go modal, or you
只要你去模态,或者你
even push in the navigation controller, these are all
甚至推动导航控制器,这些都是
managed by a class called a UI Presentation Controller,
由一个类称为UI表示控制器,
it controls the presentation of an MVC,
它控制MVC的演示,
Now, we're not gonna have time to talk about that, you can
现在,我们不会有时间去谈论,你可以
actually build your own presentation in folders that
实际上建立自己的文件夹中
present MVCs, and other ways that you want,
mvc,和其他方式,你想要的,
Pretty rare to do it, but you see it sometimes in apps, or
非常罕见的,但有时你看到它在应用程序,或
things slide out in a certain way, or whatever,
事情以某种方式滑出,等等,
But, in the popover case,
但是,在弹出窗口的情况下,
we're just gonna talk about the,
我们要谈论的,
this, presentation control a little bit, because there's
表示控制一点,因为有
a sub class of it called UI PopoverPresentationController,
它叫UI PopoverPresentationController的子类,
And it has a few interesting bars in it, like, what arrow,
有一些有趣的酒吧,喜欢,箭头,
what direction is the arrow from the popover allowed to
是什么方向的箭头从允许弹窗
point, okay?
点,好吗?
The system automatically figures out where to bring
系统会自动计算出在哪里
the popover up, but it will try to make the arrow point in
弹出窗口,但它会试图让箭头点
one of the directions that you allow, also this is where this
你允许的一个方向,也在这里
popover presentation controller is a thing where
弹出窗口显示控制器是一个事情的地方
you specify the rectangle and view that they are should
你指定矩形和认为,他们应该
point at, if it's not pointing in a bar button icon, or
点,如果它不是指向一个工具栏按钮图标,或
a button, or something like that,
一个按钮,或类似的东西,
And where do you configure all this
和你在哪里配置
UIPopoverPresentationContro- ller stuff?
UIPopoverPresentationContro——我东西?
You do it in your prepare, when you prepare for
你做准备,当你准备
a popover segue, you're going to do that,
弹窗segue,你要做的,
so, the code looks kind of like this,
所以,代码看起来有点像这样,
Here's a typical prepare for segue that is preparing for
这是一个典型的准备segue准备
a popover segue, it looks the same,
弹窗segue,看起来一样的,
all the green is the same as any other segue,
所有的绿色其它segue是一样的,
But then there's the yellow that's different
但还有黄色的区别
I'm creating this local variable,
我创建这个局部变量,
I'm calling it PPC, so that it fits on my slide,
我称之为PPC,所以它适合我的幻灯片上,
but that's not a good variable name,
但这并不是一个好的变量名,
PPC equals VC which is the View Controller that I'm
PPC = VC是我的视图控制器
segueing to give me it's popover presentation
segue给我弹窗表示
controller,
控制器,
When I get that popover presentation controller, and
当我得到这个弹窗显示控制器
you can go look at the documentation for it, but
你可以看看它的文档,但是
one of the things it can do is permitted arrow directions is,
它可以做的一件事是允许的箭头方向,
Will let you set the arrow directions to right, left,
会让你设置箭头方向向右,左,
right, up, down or here I've set it to any, which means
右,上,下或在这里我将它设置为任何,这意味着
any, I'll let the arrow point in any direction, all right?
任何,我会让箭头指向任何方向,对吧?
In addition to doing things like arrow directions,
除了做事情像箭头的方向,
this popover presentation controller also has
这个弹窗表示控制器也有
a delegate,
一个委托,
Now why does it need a delegate?
现在为什么需要委托吗?
Well the delegate is used to control this adaptation
委托是用于控制这种适应
behavior,
的行为,
Now the popover, when you have a popover, you'd like to have
现在弹出窗口,当你有一个弹出窗口,你想要
your storyboard just have a popover so
你的故事板只有一个弹出窗口
that when it works on an iPad it's nice,
在iPad上,当它工作很高兴,
It's in a popover but when you're on iPhone,
它在弹窗在iPhone,但当你
especially when you're in a horizontally compact
特别是当你在一个水平紧凑
environment you don't want to use a popover,
环境你不想使用弹出窗口,
There's usually not enough room,
没有足够的空间,通常是
it's just too crowded to put a popover in there, instead,
太拥挤的一个弹窗,相反,
you wanna do this full screen,
你想做这个全屏,
And as I said before,
正如我之前所说的,
the system will automatically adapt to the fact that you're
系统将自动适应你的事实
in a horizontally compact environment, and
水平在一个紧凑的环境,
it will make it full screen instead,
它将使全屏相反,
But via this delegate, this pop over presentation for
但是通过这个委托,这个流行在演讲
a delegate, you can control that adaptation,
适应一个委托,您可以控制,
Behavior you can prevent it, you can modify it, so
行为你可以阻止它,您可以修改它,所以
let's talk a little bit about how that works,
让我们谈谈这是如何工作的,
So this adaptation to the size classes let's just look at
这适应大小类让我们看看
the code right off the bat,
马上的代码,
This delegate method of the pop over presentation
这个流行的委托方法演示
controller is called adaptive presentation style for
控制器被称为自适应表示风格
controller trait collection,
控制器的特征集合,
And, what this is basically asking is,
这基本上是问,
I'm about to present this controller, the argument
我要现在这个控制器,论点
there, in an environment with this trait collection,
在一个环境特征集合,
Remember trait collections are like horizontal size class,
记得特征集合就像水平大小类,
vertical size class,
垂直尺寸类,
And, it's asking you to return what kind of adaptation
,它要求你返回什么样的适应
you want to do?
你想做什么?
So, you can return none, and it will not adapt,
所以,你可以返回,也不会适应,
it'll just do it like a popover,
它会像一个弹出窗口,
This how you can get a popover on your iPhone just implement
这样你可以得到一个弹出窗口你的iPhone上实现
this delegate method and return none, okay?
这个委托方法并返回没有?
,None, if you do that it won't adapt,
,没有,如果你不适应,
Now you could return other things in here like
现在您可以返回其他的事情在这里
,fullScreen or ,overfullScreen and by doing so
,全屏或者overfullScreen和通过这样做
you control how the popover's going to look and
你控制如何弹出窗口的外观和
adapt to different trade collections,
适应不同贸易集合,
Okay, hopefully, we'll have time for
好的,希望我们有时间
that in the demo maybe not, but we'll see,
在演示也许不是,但我们将会看到,
The other thing you can do, which is kinda cool when
另一件你能做的,就是有点酷的时候
it adapts, is I might have a popover, and
我可能会有一个弹出窗口,它适应和
since popovers don't have cancel buttons,
因为弹窗没有取消按钮,
They don't need cancel buttons,
他们不需要取消按钮,
cuz I can touch anywhere outside the popover, and
因为我可以在任何地方联系外窗,
it cancels it,
取消它,
Okay, so I don't need a cancel button, but on a,
好的,我不需要一个取消按钮,但是在一个,
when it adapts to full screen modal on an iPhone,
当它适应全屏模式在iPhone上,
I do need a cancel button cuz I can't click anywhere else,
我需要一个取消按钮因为我不能点击其他地方,
It's taken over my entire screen, so
占据了我的整个屏幕
I want to put a cancel button,
我想把一个取消按钮,
So to put a cancel button up there, maybe I want to put it
所以,给一个取消按钮,也许我想把它
in a navigation controller so that I can fit a cancel button
在导航控制器,这样我就可以适应一个取消按钮
at the top, a bar button item, right?
在顶部,一个工具栏按钮项,对吧?
I mean, I could put the cancel button somewhere inside my
我的意思是,我可以把取消按钮在我的地方
view controller and then just take it out when I'm on iPad,
视图控制器,然后把它当我在iPad上,
iPhone, or whatever,
iPhone,等等,
But maybe what I wanna do is have it be in the navigation
但也许我要做的是在导航
bar of a navigation controller,
栏导航控制器,
But again, only when I'm adapting and
但是,只有当我适应
so this will let you that,
这将让你,
This one called Presentation Controller,
这个叫做表示控制器,
View Controller for adaptive presentation style,
视图控制器的自适应表示风格,
is saying, what view controller should I use
是说,我应该使用视图控制器
when I adapt to this presentation style?
当我适应这个演讲风格吗?
Okay, and that presentation style over full screen or
好吧,表示在全屏或风格
pop over or full screen,
流行或全屏幕,
And so here is where you might want to say I'm gonna
所以在这里,你可能想说我要
return a navigation controller with the controller that
返回一个导航控制器的控制器
would normally disappear in a pop over inside of it
通常会消失在一个流行的吗
as it's root view controller,
根视图控制器,
Okay, so this is kind of a cool way to do substitute,
好了,这是一种很酷的方式替代,
another, like, usually a navigation controller,
另一个,比如,通常导航控制器,
another MVC that you'll wrap around the MVC you're
另一个MVC,你会环绕MVC
trying to present,
努力现在,
So the return values of this is actually
所以这实际上的返回值
another ViewController,
另一个ViewController,
Okay, so it's kinda fun controlling that adaption
好的,所以它有点有趣的控制,适应
stuff, there's another important issue about popovers
的东西,还有一个重要的问题关于弹窗
by the way, which is size,
顺便说一下,这是大小,
Now, by default,
现在,在默认情况下,
a Popover comes in size that kind of is like
弹窗的大小的
an iPhone in portrait, that's kind of it's default size,
iPhone在肖像,这是它的默认大小,
And if it doesn't really know what size the stuff is inside,
如果它不知道里面的东西是什么尺寸,
that's the best it can do,
这是最好的,
But you can control their size, make it a lot better,
但你可以控制自己的大小,使它更好,
by having the MVC that's being presented, implement, or
通过MVC的呈现,实现,或
set, this var called preferred content size,
集,这种变量称为首选内容大小,
And that just says, this is the size I want to be
只是说,这是我想要的大小
in a popover, basically or in any environment, really,
基本上在一个弹出窗口,或在任何环境中,真的,
But this is my preferred size to be and
但这是我的首选大小
so, again if we have time can do this in our demo as well,
所以,如果我们有时间可以在我们的演示,
You want to return here the smallest size
你想在这里返回最小的大小
that you look good in and then when your popover comes up,
你看起来很好,然后当你的弹出窗口出现,
it'll use this size,
它将使用这个尺寸,
If you don't set this size,
如果你不设置这个尺寸,
you're gonna kind of get this default size,
你会得到这个默认大小,
it depends on whether in portrait,
这取决于在肖像,
landscape, iPad, whatever,
景观,iPad,无论如何,
It's gonna give you a somewhat standardized size,
它会给你一个标准化的尺寸,
Okay the last segue we're going to talk about here is
好了最后segue我们这里要讲的是
embed segues, these are really cool, really powerful,
嵌入而已,这些都是很酷的,真正的强大,
Segues is basically a segue where you put another aVCs
segue基本上是一个segue你把另一个车型
self,view it's top of a view inside another view hierarchy,
的自我,把它的一个视图在另一个视图层次结构,
so this embedding view controllers inside another
这里面嵌入视图控制器
view controllers,
视图控制器,
Okay really cool thing to be able to do and
好的可以做和很酷的事情
Xcode makes this super easy,
Xcode让这个超级简单,
you're just gonna go down to your object palate,
你要去你对象口感,
And look for container view and
并寻找容器视图和
drag that container view out, it looks just like a view,
把容器视图拖出来,看起来就像一个视图,
You're gonna put auto layout on it, wherever you want and
你要把自动布局,无论你想要的
itself,view is gonna appear embedded in the view hierarchy
本身,视图会出现嵌在视图层次结构
of the thing you dragged it into,
你把它拖进,
It's really quite a normal segue,
很正常的继续,
it seems weird cuz it's like you're embedding this thing
似乎奇怪的因为它就像你嵌入这个东西
but, it's a fairly normal seque in there,
但是,这是一个相当正常的seque,
You can name it, you get to prepare for
你可以命名它,你要做好准备
seque and all that stuff,
seque和所有的东西,
You can see here,
你可以看到,
the little gray thing next to this container,
小灰的这个容器,
that's the view appearing inside the big
这就是观点出现在大
light blue view hierarchy on the left,
浅蓝色的视图层次在左边,
And on the right is just an entire NVC that you get to
右边是你得到整个签证中心
configure any class you want, any UI you wanna put in there,
配置你想要的任何类,任何UI你想放在那里,
And that's all just gonna appear inside that box on
这就是要出现在那个盒子
the blue side, okay?
蓝色的一面,好吗?
One thing to be really careful about embed segues,
有一件事非常小心嵌入而已,
it's no different than any other segue,
它比其他任何segue没有不同,
in that when it happens,,
当它发生的时候,,
When the prepare happens, none of the outlets are set In that
准备时,没有一个机构设置
MBC that you're embedded okay?
MBC嵌入你明白吗?
So a lot of times people they're embedding this other
所以很多时候他们嵌入另一个人
MBC and they want to be setting all kinds of outlet
MBC,他们想要设置各种各样的插座
in the thing they're embedding,
在当他们嵌入,
But you can't because none of those outlets have been set,
但是你不能因为这些网点设置,
you're in prepare, you're really early,
你在准备,你真早,
So almost always what we do here is we grab the entire MBC
这里几乎总是我们所做的是我们整个MBC抓住
and prepare and hold on to it,
和准备,抓住它,
And then later in our view did load when all valve is loaded
然后在我们看来并加载所有阀加载时
then do we start talking MBC and
然后我们开始MBC和说话
tell it to you know set its outlets or whatever,
告诉它你知道设置它的网点,
So 90% of the time in the prepare for
所以90%的时间准备
an embed segue we grab on to the MVC that we're embedding
一个嵌入segue我们抓住MVC,嵌入
okay which is just going to be the segue's destination right?
好了这就是segue的目的地?
That's the seg that's the MBC we're segueing to,
这是赛格MBC我们segue,
Now I'm gonna do all demo the rest of the way here, so
现在我要做的所有演示剩下的路,
I'm gonna give you a little what's coming up here,
我要给你一点什么来这里,
So on Wednesday i'm gonna be talking about alerts and
我周三会谈论警报和
action seats sheets and also notifications and
表并通知和行动席位
the application life cycle,
应用程序生命周期,
So the application life cycle's all those methods in,
所以应用程序生命周期的所有这些方法,
Next week, on Monday is the Accessibility lecture,
下周,周一是可访问性讲座,
Also Monday, slides are due if you want to
周一,幻灯片是由于如果你想
participate in the alternate final,
参与备用决赛,
You have to submit them by Monday,
你必须将它们提交到周一,
if you don't submit them by Monday, sorry,
如果你不将它们提交到周一,对不起,
you can't do the alternate final,
你不能做备用,
But then that's the only thing you do,
但是你做的唯一的事,
you don't have to sign up or anything,
你不需要注册或任何东西,
Just submit your slides by Monday and
只是被周一提交你的幻灯片
then Wednesday will be the alternate final,
然后周三将备用的决赛,
So, the demo I'm gonna do right now is we're gonna take
演示,我现在要做的是我们需要的
FaceIt and
FaceIt和
we're going to add all four of those segue Ways to it,
我们要添加的所有四个segue方式,
Okay, all the I just talked about we're gonna
好吧,我只是讲我们要
put them all in there in one little app here,
把他们都在这里的一个小程序,
So, let's go over to faces, there's faces,
所以,让我们去的脸,脸,
All right, so you guys remember faces,
好了,所以你们记住的脸,
very simple little app,
很简单的小程序,
It had this little emotions view controller and
这个小情绪视图控制器和
we had three emotions, sad, happy, and worried,
我们有三个情绪,悲伤,快乐,和担心,
And when we clicked on it,
当我们点击它,
it would show a face that showed that emotion,
它会显示一张脸表明情感,
So, I'm gonna actually before I dive into these segues,
所以,我要在我深入这些而已,
kind of enhance this whole app slightly,
提高整个应用略,
remember when we did our face view controller way back when?
还记得我们我们面对视图控制器的时候吗?
One thing is,
有一件事是,
And we wanted to do squinting, but we couldn't do squinting,
我们想做斜视,但我们做不到眯着眼,
Remember why?
还记得为什么吗?
Because our face view only could do eyes open or
因为我们只能睁着眼睛或脸视图
eyes closed,
闭上眼睛,
So we didn't really have an option to do squinting,
所以我们没有一个选项眯着眼,
so we just kinda had this, okay,
所以我们就有点这个,好吧,
well, we'll just say that is your,
好吧,我们就说,是你的,
Okay, we had the punt, essentially,
好的,我们有,从本质上讲,
So, I'm gonna make it, so we don't have to punt,
所以,我要让它,所以我们不需要,
What I'm gonna do is,
我要做的是什么,
remember we did that blinking face view controller?
记得我们眨眼面临视图控制器吗?
I'm gonna make squinting be blinking, okay?
我要让眯着眼闪烁,好吗?
Squinting and blinking aren't the same thing,
斜视和闪烁的不是一样的,
but kind of like repeatedly squinting,
但就像反复眯着眼,
So, we're gonna make it so
所以,我们要让它如此
that works, so how are we gonna do that?
工作,所以我们要怎么做呢?
We no longer have to punt here, so
我们不再需要平底船,所以
we'll just not do anything if someone says squinting, and
我们就不做任何事情如果有人说眯着眼,和
you remember that all of our blinking code is in this
你还记得我们所有的闪烁的代码
subclass here blinking a face view controller,
子类在这里闪烁一脸视图控制器,
So, we'll go ahead and make our update UI overridable and
所以,我们要让我们的更新UI重写的和
we'll go to our blinking face view controller here and
我们将去我们这里的闪烁的脸视图控制器
override it, so I'm just gonna override update UI,
覆盖它,所以我要覆盖更新UI,
Of course I wanna call funk or a funk update UI,
当然我想叫恐慌或恐慌更新UI,
and of course I wanna call my supers update UI, so that
当然我想打电话给我的管理员更新UI,因此
the mouth and other stuff and the eyes themselves can all,
嘴巴和其他东西,眼睛本身都可以,
then I'm gonna say that my blinking, whether or
然后我会说我眨眼,不管
Be set, But
组,但
not I'm blinking, is equal to our model,
不是我眨眼,等于我们的模型,
which is our expressions,
这是我们的表情,
Eyes,
的眼睛,
If those are equal to squinting,
如果这些都等于眯着眼,
So, if we're squinting, then I'm gonna be blinking,
如果我们眯着眼,然后我要闪烁,
Everybody see what I did there?
每个人都明白我在做什么吗?
So that's it, I just [LAUGH] upgraded blanking face for
就是这样,我只是[笑]升级消隐的脸
now if you set your model to have squinting, as your,
如果你设置你的模型有斜视,像你,
your controller,
你的控制器,
as part of your model,then it will blink,
作为模型的一部分,那么它会眨眼,
Now, we made this
现在,我们做了这个
blink view controller kind of a demo thing,
眨眼视图控制器的演示,
I made it every time it appears it starts blinking,
我每次都让它看起来它开始闪烁,
Every time it disappears it stops blinking,
每次它消失停止闪烁,
I don't really want that now,
我不想,现在,
Now, I want it to blink when it's squinting and
现在,我想要眨眼的时候眯着眼
not otherwise but
不但是
I also still only want it to blink when I'm on screen,
我也仍然只希望它眨眼当我在屏幕上,
I don't want my timer blinking when I'm not even up here,
我不想让我的计时器闪烁时我甚至不,
So, I'm gonna change this blinking thing here to can
所以,我要改变这种闪烁的东西来
So, let's add a new private var up here,
所以,让我们添加一个新的私人var,
blink,
眨眼,
can blink start out as false,
眨眼可以是假的,
And so here if I appear, I'll say I can blink and
这里如果我出现,我就说我可以眨眼
even say blink if needed at this point because maybe
甚至说如果需要在这一点上,因为也许眨眼
someone set us to blinking while we weren't there and
有人让我们闪烁,而我们没有
when we disappear I'm gonna say can blink was false so
当我们点击可以眨眼间就会消失是假的
I'm not allowed to blink,
我不能眨眼,
And then, in blink if needed I'll just say If I'm blinking,
然后在眨眼,如果需要我就说如果我眨眼,
and I can blink, then I'll go ahead and do my blinking,
我可以眨眼,然后我会继续做我的闪烁,
One other little thing that I want to do here is to not,
另一个小的事情我想做的是,
if I'm in the middle of a blink, okay, this timer,
如果我在一个眨眼,好吧,这个计时器,
and I get another request to blink,
我让另一个请求眨眼,
I don't want to start another timer,
我不想开始另一个定时器,
Okay, so I'm gonna have another private var var here
好的,所以我要有另一个私有变量var
which I'm gonna call in a blink which is whether I'm
我将称之为眨眼这是我
in the middle of a blink, let's start that as false,
在一个眨眼,让我们开始是错误的,
And, so I'll also check it here and we're not in a blink,
,所以我也会检查在这里,我们不是在一个眨眼,
So, then I'll just set a blank here to true and
然后我就设置一个空白来真实
then when we get out the other side down here I'll set in
当我们离开这里我会在另一面
a blank to false,
一个空白为false,
So, all I did was upgrade my blank view controller,
所以,我所做的是升级我的空白视图控制器,
so be able to be controlled by it's model rather then
所以可以由它的模型而不是控制
being a demo thing,
做一个演示,
Everybody cool with what I did there?
每个人都明白我所做的吗?
Minor little upgrade,
轻微的小升级,
Now the next thing I wanna do is,
接下来我要做的是,
What we're gonna do for
我们要做的
our demo segues is, we're gonna, if you remember in the,
我们会,我们的演示segue如果你记得的,
Self question mark here,
自我问号,
If you remember in our storyboard here,
如果你还记得我们的故事板,
We're kind of fixed to these three different emotions,
我们固定的这三种不同的情感,
that's all we have,
这就是我们,
Well, I'm gonna make it so
好吧,我要让它如此
that we can hit an add button, and add another emotion,
我们可以打一个add按钮,并添加另一个情感,
Okay, as many emotions as we want,
好的,我们想要尽可能多的情绪,
that's what we're gonna do,
这就是我们要做的,
So, we're gonna have a modal segue to that theme,
所以,我们要有一个模态segue主题,
we'll unwind to bring it back,
我们将会放松,
We'll make it work on pop over,
我们会让它工作在流行,
we'll embed the little blinking face view,
我们将嵌入小闪烁的脸看来,
We're gonna do all kinds of segue stuff here,
我们会做各种各样的segue东西,
But first we have to convert this to something that we can
但首先我们必须把这个东西
add more to,
添加更多的,
So, we can't have this three buttons like this,
所以,我们不能有这样的这三个按钮,
basically not going to work,
基本上不会工作,
So, we need a different kind,
所以,我们需要一种不同,
And what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna use, there's not much
我要做的是我要用,没什么
code in this emotions view controller as it is,
代码在这个情感视图控制器,
It just got this,
它只是有这个,
Little dictionary of the three things, and
小字典的三件事,
then it does prepare,
然后做准备,
So, I'll keep as much code as I can here,
所以,我会保持尽可能多的代码,
So, but what I'm gonna do is make it a table
所以,但是我要做的是一个表
ViewController,
Okay, so I'm just gonna turn this emotions thing into a
好的,所以我要把这感情的事情变成一个
table ViewController, cuz it's real easy to add more rows,
ViewController表,因为它是真正容易添加更多的行,
So, I'm just gonna say, this is a UITableViewController
所以,我只是想说,这是一个UITableViewController
instead and I'm gonna have to change
相反,我要改变
my model a little bit here, from being a dictionary,
我的模型一点在这里,从一个字典,
I'm just gonna have it be an array of tuples, where this
我想它是一个数组的元组,这地方
name of the emotion, and then the expression are in a tuple,
情感的名称,然后表达在一个元组,
And we'll have it in an array like that, so
我们会有一个数组,所以
I'm just gonna replace this whole thing with an array,
我要把这整个换成一个数组,
Of tuples but otherwise it's the same exact data,
的元组,但否则是一样的数据,
It's just this it's an array of tuples or
它就在一个元组或数组
one thing is the name like sad, happy and
有一件事是这个名字像悲伤,快乐,
the other is the expression, the eyes and mouth whatever,
另一个是表情,眼睛和嘴,
Since I've also made this a var, so
因为我也做了这个一个var,所以
that we can add more of them to it over time,
我们可以添加更多的人随着时间的推移,
Okay, now, we of course, this broke our prepare, but
好的,现在,我们当然,这打破了我们的准备,但是
we'll fix that in a second,
我们将解决这个问题,
Let's go back to our storyboard and add this thing,
让我们回到故事板和添加这个东西,
So, I'm gonna make a table view, so
所以,我要做一个表格视图
let's go over here to utilities windows, and
我们去这里工具窗口,
grab ourselves a table view controller, and
抓住自己一个表格视图控制器,
put it out here,
在这里,
Here's our table view,
这是我们的表视图,
Of course I wanna set this identity to be this emotions
当然我想设置这个身份是这个情绪
view controller which I can do because I changed it to be
视图控制器,我能做的,因为我改变了
And then, raise it to make it back to being th root
然后,提高它,让它回到根
a table view,
一个表格视图,
view controller of this navigation controller,
视图控制器导航控制器,
Look that up, and remember we had these three segues that
看了,记得我们有这三个segue
would segue from those three separate buttons over here,
将从这三个独立的按钮,继续
Well, I still am gonna need the segue,
好吧,我还是需要继续,
cuz I gotta show the emotion,
因为我要显示的情感,
So, I'm just gonna Ctrl drag over to here, and
所以,我要Ctrl拖到这里,和
create a new segue,
创建一个新的segue,
I'm gonna split through here, so it's gonna be show detail,
我要通过分裂,所以它会显示细节,
And we'll call this one right here, this segue,
我们叫这个,这segue,
How about show emotion?
显示情绪怎么样?
That's what it does, right?
这就是它的作用,对吧?
It shows an emotion when you click on it,
它显示了一种情感,当你点击它,
And, we'll wanna configure this table view,
我们想要配置这个表格视图,
as well right here,
也在这里,
We'll have the cells be just basic,
我们会有细胞只是基本,
One piece of text in there, that's be like happy or
一段文字,这是快乐或
sad, or whatever,
难过的时候,等等,
And we'll have reused identifier would be like
就像我们要重用标识符
emotion cell,
感情细胞,
Let's say,
比方说,
Okay, everybody cool with all that?
好吧,每个人都很酷吗?
Maybe we'll even put the title we have this title if you
也许我们甚至可以把标题我们有这个标题如果你
remember in motions the name of that table right there,
记得在运动,表的名称,
So that's all that we need to do to fix our UI,
这是我们需要做的一切来修复我们的UI,
So, we just need to fix our motions view controller to be
所以,我们只需要修复我们的动作视图控制器
a table view controller now and
现在一个表格视图控制器
set this old, kind of thing that it was before,
设置这个旧的,之前的事情,
So, let's go ahead and fix this navigation first,
所以,我们先去解决这个导航,
Remember in that case we were using the identifier of
记得在这种情况下我们使用的标识符
the segue to figure out whether we were sad,
segue找出我们是否悲伤,
happy or whatever,
快乐的,
In this case we're just gonna look at the row and
在这种情况下我们要看看行和
index it into our nice, new model up here,
指数为我们好,新模型,
So, we can get rid of this let identifier equals identifier,
所以,我们可以摆脱这个标识符=标识符,
And clearly, we're not getting the expression using that
显然,我们不能使用该表达式
dictionary anymore,
字典了,
So, everyone remembers table view?
所以,每个人都记得表视图?
We just wanna get the cell, so we're gonna let the cell equal
我们只想得到细胞,所以我们要让细胞相等
the sender as a UI table view cell,
发送方UI表视图单元格,
And then, we wanna get the index path of that cell so
然后,我们想要的索引路径细胞
we know which row it is,
我们知道它是哪一行,
So, we're gonna say let index path,
所以,我们会说让索引路径,
Equal the table view,
等于表格视图,
Index, path for the cell,
细胞指数、路径,
Okay, so long as we're able to get that indexPath out of
好吧,只要我们能够得到indexPath走出
there, then setting the expression
在那里,然后设置表达式
in our faceViewController is really easy,
在我们faceViewController真的很容易,
It's just going to be our model, emotionalFaces
这只是我们的模型,emotionalFaces
indexPath,row and here, we want the expression, right?
indexPath,行,在这里,我们想要表达,对吧?
We want this part of the tuple,
我们希望这个元组的一部分,
Okay, similarly for saving the title, we're not coming
好的,同样保存标题,我们不是来了
from a button anymore, we're coming from table view row,
从一个按钮了,我们来自表格视图行,
So we want to do the same thing but we want the name,
所以我们想做同样的事情,但我们希望这个名字,
cut to this topol,
减少这个托
Okay, that's all we have to do there,
好了,这就是我们要做的,
that was easy to convert, everybody cool?
这很容易转换,每个人都很酷?
So, now we've got navigation working,
所以,现在我们有导航工作,
What's the most important thing we need to do in a table
什么是最重要的事情我们需要做一个表
view to get it working?
为了让它工作吗?
We need to implement its UITableViewDataSource, right?
我们需要实现它的需要,对吗?
Get the data in the table,
表中的数据,
Super simple on this ca, case we haven't seen numberofrows
超级简单的ca,我们还没有看到numberofrows
and section, that's just going to return
节,就会返回
our emotional faces of their account,
我们的情感面临他们的账户,
However many of these emotional faces that we have
然而这些情绪面孔
up here and then we need cell for row and index path,
然后我们需要细胞行和索引路径,
That's also easy, we'll get the cell by dequeing,
也很简单,我们会得到双端队列的细胞,
dequeueReusableCell(with identifyer,
dequeueReusableCell(与识别,
We called it emotion cell, I think, there's the index class
我认为我们称之为感情细胞,指数类
and we would have the cells text label text equal
我们会有细胞文本标签文本相等
the emotion faces name right index path row,
情绪面孔的名字正确索引路径行,
The name that's the name and puppies are whatever and
名称和小狗的名字是什么
when we return this, so better if we just converge this to
当我们返回,所以如果我们只是收敛这个更好
your table view was easy hope all of you your super familiar
你的表视图很容易希望你们非常熟悉
with table view,
表视图,
After all this so let's go ahead and run and
毕竟这所以让我们继续和运行
make sure that we've got our new upgraded version of
确保我们有我们的新版本的升级
this emotions thing working well, we didn't forget
这感情的事情工作,我们没有忘记
some identifier somewhere or something like that,
一些标识符之类的地方,
Okay, here we go here's our app, here's our three
好的,我们这里是我们的应用程序,这是我们三人
things in our table view, that's looking good so far,
事情在我们的表视图,看上去不错,
Let's click on one that looks sad that looks happy,
让我们点击一个看起来伤心,看上去很幸福,
okay, we've converted our thing nicely, so
好的,我们转换我们的东西好,所以
now we're gonna dive into these segues,
现在我们要深入这些而已,
The first we're gonna do is add a button up here
首先我们要做的就是添加一个按钮
which is gonna do a modal segue to bring up
要做一个模态segue抚养吗
an emotion editing gear controller, something that
一种情感编辑装置控制器,东西
lets us create a new one of these emotions, okay?
让我们创建一个新的这些情绪,好吗?
So it's gonna have to let us specify the name like sad,
所以要让我们指定名称像悲伤,
happy or worried and
开心还是担心,
this is gonna have to list best by the mouth and
这是要最好的嘴和列表
the eyes, okay?
眼睛,好吗?
And that's all it's gonna do, all right,
它会做的,好吧,
so, how do we do that?
那么,我们如何做呢?
Let's go back to our story board and
让我们回到我们的故事板
we need to drag out the story board that is going to be
我们需要拖出的故事板
this mo- modal view controller,
这莫-模态视图控制器,
didn't get a chance to do this earlier in the quarter,
没有得到一个机会来做这个季度早些时候,
Just because I
只是因为我
I'm gonna make the UI for this thing be a static table view,
我要让这个UI是一个静态的表视图,
Right, we've done dynamic table views, but
对的,我们所做的动态表视图,但是
we haven't done a static one,
我们没有做一个静态的,
So, let's go ahead and do a static one, so
让我们来做一个静态的,所以
I'm gonna drag out a table view,
我要拖出一个表格视图,
Here it is, right here and, I'm going to make it static,
在这里,在这里,我要让它静止,
so I'm gonna click on the table view in here, and
所以我要在这里点击表格视图,和
change it from being content dynamic to content static,
改变它的内容动态内容静态,
By the way, didn't I really talk about this, I should of,
顺便说一下,我真的没有谈这个,我应该的,
I suppose,
我想,
But, how do you define how many rows there are in
但是,你如何定义中有多少行
a static table, okay?
一个静态表,好吗?
You're gonna hold control shift and click on the table,
你要保持控制转变,点击表,
so that you can drill down to what you want,
这样你就可以钻到你想要的,
You don't want the controller,
你不想要的控制器,
you don't want the table view, you want the section okay,
你不想要的表视图,你想要的部分好了,
because, in a static table you could have multiple sections,
因为,在静态表可以有多个部分,
You wanna be able to edit a certain section,
你想编辑一个特定的部分,
you click on that, now it's selected,
你点击,现在是选择,
And so in the Inspector Table View section,
所以在检查员表视图部分,
you see rows, and I can change this to be 4 rows,
你看行,和我可以改变这是4行,
Now, why do I need 4 rows?
为什么我需要4行吗?
Well, I need the name, I need the eyes, I need the mouth and
好了,我需要这个名字,我需要眼睛,嘴,我需要
also I'm gonna have one row which is a a preview of what
我要还一行的预览
the face is gonna look like, okay?
面对会看起来像,好吗?
So as you can see, as you're choosing your eyes and mouth,
所以你可以看到,当你选择你的眼睛和嘴巴,
what you are actually doing, so
你是做什么,所以
that's why you need four rows,
这就是为什么你需要四行,
You can also put headers and footers in here, but
你也可以把页眉和页脚,但是
I actually am going to leave this in plain style,
我要离开这个朴素的风格,
And not have any headers and footers cuz they kind of,
并没有因为他们的设置页眉和页脚时,
doesn't need any headers and footers,
不需要任何页眉和页脚,
All these four rows go together,
所有这四个行混合在一起,
Okay, so we don't need to do that, we of course are going
好的,我们不需要这样做,我们当然会
to need a subclass of UI table view controller
需要一个子类的UI表格视图控制器
to control this MVC, so let's go ahead and create that,
控制这个MVC,所以让我们继续和创造,
The subclass of UI Tableview controller,
的子类uitableview控制器,
Now this is an interesting naming thing,
现在这是一个有趣的命名,
right here, I'm gonna call this my
在这里,我要打电话给我
ExpressionEditorViewControl- ler,
ExpressionEditorViewControl - l,
Notice I'm not calling it my
注意到我不叫它
ExpressionEditorTableViewCont- roller,
ExpressionEditorTableViewCont辊,
This is purely and art of programming thing I tend to
这是我倾向于纯粹的编程和艺术的事情
not name my static table views with the word table in there,
不是名字我的静态表视图与词表,
And the reason for that is I'm mostly using static table here
原因是我主要使用静态表
just to help me layout the UI,
只是为了帮助我UI布局,
I'm not using it's table viewness very much,
我不使用它的表viewness很多,
Okay, like I would to be with dynamic rose so,
好的,我将与动态增长,
I tend to not but the word table it's up to you,
我倾向于不但是一词表由你决定,
You can certainly called a expression editor table view
你当然可以称为表达式编辑器表视图
if you wanted
如果你想要
I like my expression editor view controller but do you
我喜欢我的表达式编辑器视图控制器但你
understand why I'm calling expression editor, right?
明白为什么我打电话表达式编辑器,对吗?
Because it's going to edit an expression,
因为它会编辑一个表达式,
a facial expression here,
一个表情,
We'll put it in the same place,
我们会把它放在同一个地方,
we'd put everything else, here it is,
在这里,我们要把一切
I'm gonna clean out all this stuff right here,
我要清理这些东西在这里,
I don't need any of this, table view data source stuff,
我不需要任何的表视图数据源的东西,
because this is a static cell,
因为这是一个静态的细胞,
I'm not gonna allow deletion, or anything like that,
我不会允许删除,或类似的东西,
we're not gonna be Doing navigation out of it, so
我们不会做导航,
we have this nice empty expression editor,
我们有一个好的空表达式编辑器,
And let's make sure that in our story board that we go and
我们确保我们的故事板,我们去
change the identity of this guy to be this expression
改变这个人的身份是这个表达式
editor otherwise won't be able to wire up any outlets or
否则无法编辑任何媒体或线
any things like that,
任何类似的东西,
Okay, let's start, before we build our UI for
好的,让我们开始,在我们构建UI
this, let's just put a cancel button in here and
这一点,我们就把这里和取消按钮
get this modal segue going, so let's do the modal segue,
得到这个模态segue,让我们来做模态segue,
We're gonna modal segue from this emotions,
我们将模态segue从这个情绪,
this is where all our emotions are, sad, happy, etc,
这就是我们所有的情感,悲伤,快乐,等等,
I'm gonna put a little bar button item in there, so
我要写一个小栏按钮项目,
I'm gonna search for bar button item there it is,
我要搜索栏按钮项目就是这样,
I'm gonna drag it up here,
我要拖在这里,
When I inspect it, there's actually some pre-canned bar
当我检查它,实际上有一些预定义的酒吧
button items for common things you want to do like add,
按钮项目等常见的事情你想做添加,
which is what we're gonna do,
这是我们要做的,
cancel, redo, all these things,
取消,重做,所有这些东西,
You can pick these and they'll have standard icon,
你可以选择这些,他们会有标准图标,
standard words and So in here we are adding an emotion so
标准字在我们添加一个情感
I'm gonna hit add, happens to be a plus sign,
点击添加,恰好是一个加号,
And I'm just going to ctrl drag from that to my new
和我要ctrl拖到我的新
editing view controller and I'm not gonna do show or
编辑视图控制器和显示或我不会做
show detail, I'm gonna do present modally,
模式地展示细节,现在我要做的,
Okay that's going to take over the whole screen and
好,这是要接管整个屏幕
put this MBC up and
把这个MBC起来
allow me to add a new emotion or whatever in here,
请允许我在这里添加一个新的情感之类的,
Now, how do we get out of this?
现在,我们怎么出去呢?
If either run this right now, we'll see that it
如果现在运行这个,我们会看到它
works in a manner of speaking but it really kind of kills my
在说话的口气,但真的杀了我的
whole app, my app would be dead it seems like do that,
整个应用程序,应用程序就死了似乎这样做,
let's go here this is working fine,
我们去这里工作正常,
I click on this plus, this thing comes up, I'm dead now,
我点击这个加上,这个东西,我现在死了,
There's nothing I can do, I can't get out of here,
没有什么我能做的,我不能离开这里,
This has taken over my app and
这占据了我的应用程序
I haven't provided any way to get out of it, okay?
我没有提供任何方法,好吗?
So let's start by adding a cancel button,
通过添加一个取消按钮,开始
we're just gonna make it so we can cancel out of this,
我们要让它我们可以消掉了,
I'm gonna put it as a bar button item in a navigation
我要把它作为一个导航栏按钮项目
controller so I'm gonna pick this thing and
所以我要拿这事和控制器
say embed in navigation controller,
说嵌入在导航控制器,
Okay, so I put this in the navigation controller, so
好的,我把这个导航控制器,所以
now I can put up on top of here a cancel button,
现在我可以把这一个取消按钮,
I'm going to put it on the left,
我打算把它放在左边,
it's another bar button item,
这是另一个工具栏按钮,
There happens to be a standard one for that as well; cancel
碰巧有一个标准的,取消
and how do I make this cancel button work?
我怎么把这个取消按钮的工作吗?
How do I make it actually cancel?
我怎么让它真的取消吗?
Well, this is where I do the dismiss, so, let's wire
嗯,这就是我认为,所以,让我们电线
this up, target action to a method that does the dismiss,
这个,目标操作方法,驳回,
So, let's go into automatic mode, here,
所以,让我们进入自动模式,在这里,
we've got our new expression editor view controller,
我们有我们的新表达式编辑器视图控制器,
I'm gonna control drag from the cancel button over here,
我要控制拖的取消按钮,
Do an action okay, borrow but
做一个行动好了,借但吗
an items in the argument and I'm gonna call this cancel,
一个项目的参数,我将称之为取消,
Of course, and it's going to cancel,
当然,它将取消,
And in here, I need to dismiss,
在这里,我需要解散,
But remember, I can't send dismiss to myself, dismiss is
但请记住,我不能发送解雇自己,解散
a view controller thing but I can't dismiss myself,
一个视图控制器的事但是我不能把我自己,
I have to send it to my presenting view controller,
我必须寄给我展示视图控制器,
So all view controllers know who presented them, if any,
所以所有视图控制器知道谁提出,如果有的话,
It could be nil, okay,
它可以是零,
you might not have been presented by another one,
你可能没有被另一个了,
I'm just gonna ask my presenting view controller,
我要问一下我的展示视图控制器,
please dismiss whoever you've presented, which is me,
请把谁你了,这就是我,
And yes, please do it animated,
是的,请做动画,
And I don't need to find out when it's finished dismissing,
我不需要找到解雇,当它完成的时候,
so I'll just leave that off,
所以我就离开了,
So now, if we run and we go here and hit the plus,
现在,如果我们运行我们去这里,点击+,
Okay?
好吧?
comes up here is our table view,
这是我们的表视图,
We haven't done a UI yet but
我们没有做一个UI,但
if we cancel we goes back into dismisses us, okay?
如果我们取消回到驳斥了我们,好吗?
So we're in good shape,
所以我们的身体状况很好,
So now let's go ahead and do RUY,
现在让我们继续做标本馆,
let's go back to our storyboard here,
让我们回到故事板,
And add RUI for these four things, again we want the name
又为这四个东西添加鲁伊,我们希望这个名字
like sad happy whatever, we want a little preview face,
像悲伤快乐,我们想要一个小的预览的脸,
and then we want the eyes and the mouth,
然后我们希望眼睛和嘴巴,
So I'm just gonna start dragging this stuff out and
所以我要开始拖动这个东西出去
we'll start working on making it look good over time,
我们会努力让它随着时间的推移,看起来很不错
So for the name obviously I'll need a text field so
所以对于这个名字显然我需要一个文本字段
I'm just gonna drag that out and notice all these cells
我要拖出去,注意到所有这些细胞
are of type if you look at the cell types here,
如果你看一下类型的细胞类型,
they're all custom cells,
他们都是定制的细胞,
Because I'm gonna be putting custom UI in each of them,
因为我要把定制的UI,
We're gonna configure that in a second,
我们会在第二个配置,
What about here in our little face view thing,
在我们的小脸视图的事情呢,
What are we gonna do to show our face?
我们要做些什么来展示我们的脸?
Well, I'm gonna start by doing a face view ui view,
好吧,我要先做一个视图界面视图,
Yeah, let's put a generic UI view in here,
是的,我们把一个通用的用户界面视图,
I'll even put some nice auto layout in here on this one,
我甚至会把一些不错的自动布局在这里,
is that it, yeah,
是,是的,
and we'll do reset to suggested constraints,
我们会做重置建议限制,
check out constraints to make sure it looks good,
检查约束以确保它看起来不错,
Yeah, that looks good to me,
是的,看起来不错,
We'll inspect the identify and make it be a face view so
我们将检查识别并使它成为一个脸视图
we get a nice face in there,
我们得到一个漂亮的脸,
So that's a good face,
所以这是一个很好的脸,
So we have text field face,
所以我们有文本字段的脸,
What about for eyes and mouth?
对眼睛和嘴呢?
How are we gonna set our eyes and mouth?
我们要如何设置我们的眼睛和嘴吗?
I'm gonna use something that something that
我要用的东西
I haven't shown you yet, which is a segmented control,
我还没有向你展示,这是一个分段控制,
So segmented control looks like this,
所以分段控制是这样的,
Okay, we'll drag one in here, drag one in here as well,
好的,我们将在这里,拖着拖着在这里,
And a segmented control lets you choose from a number of
和分段控制允许您选择的
items up to maybe four or five like a fixed number of items,
物品,也许四个或五个像固定数量的项目,
So that's perfect for our eyes and
这是对我们的眼睛和完美
mouth cuz we have three kinds of eyes positions and
口因为我们有三种位置和眼睛
five kinds of, of mouth,
五种,嘴,
And when you inspect it right here,
当你检查在这里,
you can say how many different choices you want,
你可以说多少种不同的选择你想要的,
So for eyes we want three segments, and here for
所以对于眼睛我们要三个部分,并在这里
the mouth we're gonna need five,
口我们需要5个,
Okay, right frown, smile,
好的,正确的皱眉,微笑,
smirk, grin, neutral, whatever,
假笑,笑容,中性的,无论如何,
And then you can just edit these,
然后你可以编辑这些,
you just double-click on them,
你只要双击,
So here let's say eyes open here we'll say eyes closed
我们这里假设眼睛睁开闭上眼睛
and, of course, our favorite one which is squinting,
当然,我们最喜欢的一个是眯着眼,
And then down here we'll have frown and
然后下面我们会皱眉
smirk and oops sorry, neutral,
假笑,哦对不起,中性,
And what to grin I think,
笑我想什么,
then we add smile,
然后加入微笑,
Okay, so there's our UI,
好,这是我们的UI,
So we want to make some of these things look a little
所以我们要做一些这些东西看起来有点
better like this text field right here there's quite a few
好喜欢这里的文本字段有不少
things we want to set about this text field,
我们要设置文本框,
One thing is we really don't need a little border,
有一件事是我们真的不需要一个小的边界,
I zoom way in so you can see here,
我在这里你可以看到放大的方式,
We don't really need this border around,
我们真的不需要这个边界,
It's in a text field row, so
在一个文本字段行,所以
that's kind of it's own border,
这是它自己的边界,
So we're gonna go down here and say border off so
所以我们要在这里说边境了
it's not gonna have any border,
它不会有任何边界,
Also I want the font to be quite a bit larger,
我也想要的字体有点大,
let's say 24 point would be good,
假设24点就好了,
We'll have it be centered, the text will be centered,
我们会为中心,文本为中心,
There's no reason to have it left or right aligned,
没有理由让它向左或向右对齐,
Let's use place holder text, that's really cool,
让我们使用占位符文本,这是很酷的,
I'm gonna put name in here as the Placeholder text,
我要把名字在这里作为占位符文本,
That way I don't need to label on the left that says name,
这样我不需要标签左边说名字,
this is the name of this emotion,
这是这种情绪的名字,
I'll just put this placeholder there,
我就把这个占位符,
it'll be obvious to users,
这将是明显的用户,
That's the name,
的名字,
And so they'll just click there, and start typing,
所以他们会点击,开始打字,
And, also, for the keyboard,
同时,键盘,
I'm gonna have it autocapitalize every word,
我要把它autocapitalize每一个字,
So that if you say sad it will be capital S-A-D,
所以,如果你说伤心资本S-A-D,
It will just look nicer in my other table I think,
它将看起来更好的在我的其他表我认为,
And then finally, what about the auto layout here?
最后,这里的自动布局呢?
Where do we want this to appear?
我们希望这个出现在哪里?
Well I think we just want this thing to be centered in
我认为我们只是想要集中在这件事
there so I am going to pick centered horizontally and
所以我要选择集中水平和
centered vertically I just control dragged to this row,
我只是控制拖这一行,居中
And so, that's good enough,
所以,这是足够好,
You notice that it's yellow, right?
你注意到它是黄色的,对吗?
Why is it yellow?
为什么是黄色的吗?
Because my constraints don't match what's on screen,
因为我的约束不匹配在屏幕上,
So, I can fix that in my document outline,
所以,我可以解决,在我的文档大纲,
Indeed, here's that yellow,
事实上,这是黄色的,
I go up here, I click on this, I'll use update frames here to
我去这里,我点击这个,我将使用更新帧来
misplace it and moves name into the right spot,
放错地方的名字移到正确的位置,
Okay, we already have our auto layout and everything for
好的,我们已经有我们的自动布局和一切
the face view,
面对视图,
How about this guy down here?
下面这个人怎么样?
Let's us zoom in again and look,
让我们再次放大,看,
What I'm actually going to put another constraint on here to
我要把另一个约束在这里
show you a little more sophisticated constraints,
给你一个更复杂的约束,
which is do I ever want to allow this to spill of
这是我想要让这个泄漏的
the edges?
边吗?
ta-table view so narrow that it wouldn't even fit these?
表格中视图非常狭窄,甚至不适合这些吗?
And the answer is no way,
答案是否定的,
I would never want the table view to be that narrow,
我永远不会想要表视图,狭窄,
I always want it to be wide enough to at least fit
我总是想要宽至少足够健康
all these buttons,
所有这些按钮,
So I'm gonna CTRL + drag from this right edge
所以我要从这右边缘CTRL +拖
over to this to do the trailing space,
在这个落后于空间,
Okay, So great to this eye beam
好的,所以这只眼睛光束
right here that you're very similar with,
在这里,与你很相似,
We can click on it,
我们可以点击它,
Where is it? There it is,
在哪里?
But I don't actually want it to be 75,
但我不希望它是75年,
I want it to be zero, all the way over the edge,
我希望它是零,边缘,
But I don't actually don't want it to be equal to zero,
但实际上我不不想让它等于零,
Because then that means that edge is always gonna be pinned
因为那意味着边缘总是会固定
over there and that's gonna stretch my control out and
那边要伸展我的控制
I do want the secondary control to be, you know,
我想要二次控制,你知道,
fit into its text, but I don't wanna be stuck over here,
适合它的文本,但我不想被困在这里,
So what I'm gonna do is make it to be greater than or
所以我要做的是让它大于或
equal to zero,
等于零,
So we have not seen this kind of constraint,
所以我们没有见过这样的约束,
where you're not setting it equal to something,
你没有设置它等于,
you're setting it greater than equal,
你设置大于等于,
what I'm saying is, the distance between this edge and
我想说的是,这条边之间的距离和
And that's what,
这就是,
right here must be at least zero, so
这里必须至少为零,所以
it can't be negative, it can't have pushed off the edge,
它不能是负数,它不能使边缘,
You see that?
你看到了吗?
That's gonna keep my table view big enough, to do this,
会让我的表视图足够大,要做到这一点,
And now, of course,
现在,当然,
I need to do the same thing on the other side of this,
我需要做同样的事情的另一面,
I'll Ctrl+drag over here, leading space,
我会按Ctrl +拖在这里,空间,
And we'll click on this one and we'll say 0 as well, and
我们点击这个,我们说0,
we want this to be greater than or equal,
我们希望这是大于或等于,
So I'm just guaranteeing that that thing is gonna be,
我就是要保证,
greater than or equal to,
大于或等于,
Okay, now it's let's double check all of our things here,
好的,现在让我们仔细检查我们所有的东西,
So we've got the trailing space and leading space,
所以我们有领先落后于空间和空间,
So this one also I probably want in the middle, so
这个我也可能想要在中间,所以
I'm gonna Ctrl+drag,
我要Ctrl +拖,
Okay, and say I want horizontally and vertically,
好,说我想水平方向和垂直方向上,
Okay, so it's not where it's supposed to be so
好吧,这不是它应该是这样的
I can update its frame right here and it looks good,
我可以更新它的框架,它看起来很好,
It's where it's supposed to be,
它应该是,
I'm guaranteed that it's never going to spill out over
我保证永远不会溢出
the edges because I put that side constraint in,
因为我把那边约束边缘,
Let's do the exam same thing with this one right here,
让我们做这个考试一样,
CTRL + drag,
CTRL +拖,
Center it vertically,
中心垂直,
CTRL + drag,
CTRL +拖,
Center it horizontally,
其水平居中,
CTRL + drag to the edge,
CTRL +拖动边缘,
This the trailing space,
这个空间之后,
We're going here,
我们会在这里,
We want it to be greater than or
我们希望它是大于或
equal to zero, and the same thing over here,
等于零,同样的事情在这里,
This the leading edge will come out,
这个前沿,
we want that to be greater than or equal to zero,
我们希望这是大于或等于零,
Okay, get that right,
好的,得到正确的,
did I say greater than equal to there?
我说大于等于?
Yes I did,
是的,我做的,
Okay, this one also, not positioned properly,
好吧,这个也不能正确定位,
no problem, we go over here,
没问题,我们去这里,
Update frames, looking good,
更新帧,看上去不错,
Okay, a lot of layout issues,
好吧,很多布局问题,
All right, here's our UI here, looking pretty good,
好的,这里是我们的UI,看起来不错,
Let's go ahead and run this and
让我们继续,这个和运行
just see what our UI looks like, see if we,
看看我们的UI是什么样子,看看我们,
Got everything where we wanted, things are centered,
得到了我们想要的一切,都是为中心,
things are the right size, all that business,
事情是正确的大小,所有的业务,
Okay so we'll go over here,
好,我们就去这里,
bring it up, looking pretty good,
把它,看起来很好,
The only thing is, that face,
唯一的问题是,脸,
I'd like that face to be as big as possible,
我想这张脸要尽可能的大,
Look how the eyes are so
看眼睛是如此
little they're almost like solid eyes,
小他们几乎像固体的眼睛,
Really I'd like that row in the table
真的我想表中的行
to be a square since my face is a circle,
广场因为我的脸是一个圆,
I'd like it to be a square,
我想这是一个广场,
So how can I make that a square?
所以我怎么能让一个正方形吗?
Hopefully all of you know this from your homework assignment,
希望你们所有的人知道这从你的家庭作业,
How to control the height of something,
如何控制的高度,
I'm just gonna go into my code right here for
我要进入我的代码在这里
my expression editor,
我的表达式编辑器,
that row I'm gonna have the table view's height for row,
这一行我要对行表视图的高度,
And for
和
Okay? I'm gonna say if the index
好吧?
path we're talking about,
我们谈论的道路,
row equals 1 cuz that's the second one down,
行= 1因为这是第二个,
that's where my face is, I'm kind of hard wiring this,
这就是我的脸,我有点硬布线,
we could probably use constants,
我们可以使用常量,
all that stuff in here,
所有的东西在这里,
Then, I'm gonna return the table views bounds,size,width,
然后,我要返回表视图边界,大小,宽度,
So I'm going make the height equal to the width,
所以我要使高度等于宽度,
That way it'll be a square,
这将是一个广场,
otherwise I'm gonna return our superclasses,
否则我要返回我们的超类,
cuz we're overriding this function, right?
因为我们重写这个函数,对吧?
So TableView, heightForRowAt, and
所以TableView heightForRowAt和
the TableView is our TableView and the height is at
TableView是我们TableView和高度
this index path that it's asking us for right here,
这个索引路径,它要求我们在这里,
Okay?
好吧?
So, everybody got that?
所以,大家都明白了吗?
So let's run, and see if it makes that thing square,
所以让我们运行,看它是否使这个广场,
Should make that face square,
应该让那张脸广场,
All right, let's go back here,
好吧,让我们回到这里,
sure enough we've got a nice big square face here,
当然我们有一个大的方脸,
Click, and
点击,
Okay, so this is excellent,
好吧,这是优秀的,
We got our UI exactly the way we want it,
我们有我们的UI正是我们想要的方式,
Now we just need to hook up our outlets and
现在我们只需要把我们的网点和
actions to this thing,
行动,
We're gonna need outlets to these two segmented controls
我们需要这两个分段控制
And an outlet to this name, so we can get the name,
和一个出口这个名字,所以我们可以得到这个名字,
right here,
在这里,
And build an expression out of the settings of this switch,
并构建一个表达式的这个开关的设置,
And then obviously,
然后很明显,
we're gonna need to be able to set our face view to reflect
我们需要能够设置视图来反映
that as well,
,,
So let's go do that,
让我们去做,
Go back to our storyboard here,
回到我们的故事板,
That, this up, let's close that, all right,
这个,让我们接近,好吧,
Zoom in a little bit here,
放大一点,
Okay, so let's create outlets for these two things and for
好的,让我们为这两个东西和创建媒体
this name,
这个名字,
So Ctrl-drag over here,
所以Ctrl-drag这里,
Call that our nameTextField, we'll control drag from
我们称之为nameTextField,我们会控制阻力
this guy down here, we'll call this our eyeControl, and we'll
这家伙在这里,我们称之为eyeControl,我们会
drag from this one, call that our mouthControl,
从这一个阻力,我们称之为mouthControl,
Okay, so we got our nice, outlets there,
好的,我们有我们的好,网点,
Let's go ahead and think about the model of this control,
让我们继续,考虑到模型的控制,
what does it do?
它做什么?
It's an editor,
这是一个编辑器,
It edits an expression, a named expression actually,
编辑一个表达式,指定表达式实际上,
So it clearly has something which is the name, okay?
所以它显然有这个名字,好吗?
So we'll make the name,
我们会让这个名字,
we'll have that be our nameTextField,
我们会是我们nameTextField,
Text, and if we don't have a nameTextField yet,
文本,如果我们没有nameTextField然而,
like we're preloaded, we'll just return a empty string,
像我们预紧,我们就返回一个空字符串,
Okay, so that's the name part,
好了,这是一部分的名字,
And of course, we have an expression as well,
当然,我们也有一个表达式,
that's gonna be FacialExpression,
这是要FacialExpression,
And we'll return by creating a FacialExpression, and
我们将通过创建一个返回FacialExpression,
here is its constructor, we'll make it a little easier to see
这是它的构造函数,我们将使它更容易看到
when we're an arrow here like this,
当我们在这儿一个箭头,
Okay, so how are we gonna set the eyes?
好的,那么我们要如何设置眼睛吗?
We're gonna look at our eye control and
我们要看看我们的眼睛控制
see what the eyes are,
看到眼睛是什么,
How do we set the mouth?
我们如何设置嘴吗?
We're gonna look at our mouth control,
我们要看看我们的口控制,
So to make this easy,
因此为了简化,
I'm gonna make a little private var here,
我要做一个小的私人var,
Actually a let,
让,
I'm gonna call this my eyeChoices, okay, these
我要叫它eyeChoices,这些
are the three choices in my set menu control view there,
是我的设置菜单控制视图的三个选择,
it's just going to be a little array that has facial, oops,
它就是一个数组的面部,哎呀,
Z, equals an array with FacialExpression,Eyes,
与FacialExpression Z,等于一个数组,眼睛,
and we've got open, closed, and squinting, those
我们有打开,关闭,眯着眼,
are the Three different things in our segmented control,
是三个不同的东西在我们的分段控制,
So now to make this I's thing I can just return here
现在让我的事情我可以返回这里
my i choices,
我的选择,
And the index I'm gonna use is my eye control,
和索引我要用我的眼睛控制,
And the way you get which of the segments is controlled is
你得到这段控制的
picked in a segmented control is with the method in
选择在一个分段控制的方法
segmented control called selected segment index,
分段控制称为选择段指数,
Selected segment index,
选择部分指数,
And of course our eye control might not be set yet,
当然我们的眼睛控制可能没有被设置,
in which case we'll default to just doing segment 0,
在这种情况下,我们将默认为只做段0,
Okay? Does everybody see what we're,
好吧?
what we're doing there?
我们在做什么?
To do that?
这样做吗?
And same thing with the mouth,
和一样的嘴,
We'll have some mouth choices here,
我们这里有一些口的选择,
These are facialExpression,mouth,
这些都是facialExpression,嘴,
What have we got here, frown,
在这里我们得到了什么,皱眉,
We've got smirk, we've got neutral,
我们有笑容,有中性的,
we've got grin and we've got smile,
我们有笑容和我们有微笑,
Do the same thing here, we'll say mouthChoices,
做同样的事,我们会说mouthChoices,
Okay?
好吧?
So mouthControl this time, selectedSegment Index,
所以这次mouthControl,selectedSegment指数,
And again we'll default to 0,
我们将默认为0,
So everyone see how we've created our facial expression
所以每个人都看到我们创造了我们的面部表情
from our UI?
从我们的UI ?
This is essentially our model, it's a read only model,
这就是我们的模型,这是一个只读模式,
You could imagine designing this to not be read only,
你可以想象设计这不是只读,
where you might want to have this editor start with some
你可能想有这个编辑器开始与一些吗
expression you set,
表达式设置,
But we're just gonna do this to make it easy,
但是我们要这样做使它容易,
Read only,
只读,
And one other thing we want to do is whenever these
另一件事,我们要做的是当这些
are changed over here, well, for
是改变了,
now every time someone clicks on one of these we're just
现在每次有人点击其中一个我们
gonna print on the console what our expression is,
要打印在控制台上我们表达的是什么,
So let's create a little target action from this guy,
所以让我们创建一个小目标动作从这个家伙,
control drag,
控制阻力,
We'll call it updateface cuz that's
我们叫它updateface因为这是
what we're gonna need to do is update this face up here,
我们要做的就是更新这张脸,
We don't need any arguments to it,
我们不需要任何参数,
Okay so this update face is gonna have to change this face
这更新的脸是要改变这张脸
to reflect the eyes and stuff, but for now I'm just gonna say
反映了眼睛和东西,但现在我只是想说
print our name equals our expression,
打印我们的名字=我们的表达式,
So like sad equals,
就像悲伤的=。
you know frown plus closed eyes or whatever,
你知道皱眉+闭上眼睛,
Okay, and we'll have this one do the exact same thing,
好的,我们会做相同的事,
To the same action, everybody cool?
相同的动作,每个人都很酷吗?
So we just actions to make our, our thing work here,
我们只是让我们的行动,在这里工作,
So let's go run, see if our UI is basically working,
所以我们去跑,看看我们的UI基本上是工作,
It's, it needs to be hooked up to the rest of our app but
,它需要连接到我们的应用程序,但其余部分
still we wanna make sure it's it's functioning property,
我们仍然想要确保它的功能属性,
properly,
得当,
Let's add, we'll call this, here's a interesting thing,
让我们添加,我们叫这个,这是一个有趣的事情,
So, let's go here,
所以,我们去这里,
See when I click on these it selected this row,
当我点击这些选择的这一行,
I didn't want this row
我不想让这一行
to be selected like in a table view sense,
选择如表视图来说,
I just wanted it to edit this name right here so
我想这样编辑这个名字
that's not good, so we'll have to fix that,
那不是很好,所以我们必须解决这个问题,
But let's go ahead and put in a test name,
但我们在测试名称,
We'll say test, return,
我们会说测试,返回,
Return doesn't get rid of the keyboard,
返回不摆脱键盘的,
So that's bad, bad UI,
这是坏的,坏的UI,
Because now it's
因为现在是
really hard to get to these things down here,
很难得到这些东西,
I can get to them, because this is a scroll view,
我可以,因为这是一个滚动视图,
Table view is a scroll view,
表视图是一个滚动视图,
But it's still kinda bad UI,
但还是有点糟糕的UI,
So we gotta fix that as well,
所以我们要解决这个问题,
So let's pick eyes closed and
所以我们选择闭上眼睛
see if our console is saying anything and
说什么,看看我们的控制台
sure it's saying test equals eyes closed mouth frown,
肯定是说测试=闭上眼睛嘴巴皱眉,
That looks right eyes closed mouth frown,
看起来正确的闭上眼睛嘴巴皱眉,
Let's say squinting grin,
假设眯着眼笑,
Squinting grin,
眯着眼笑,
Okay so it looks like our UI is working but
所以它看起来像我们的UI但工作
it's got these two problems,
它有这两个问题,
So let's fix the problem where it's selecting this row in
让我们解决这个问题的选择这一行
the table view sense when we click in there and
表视图意义上,当我们点击,
let's fix the problem where a return key is not
让我们解决这个问题,一个返回键不是
resigning first responder and,
首先回应的辞职,
And making the keyboard go away,
并使键盘消失,
So both of those are easy to do,
所以这些都是容易做的,
We can do that most of this in a story board,
我们能做的,大多数的故事板,
So let's go back to our story board full screen here,
让我们回到故事板全屏,
So the way to make it, so it doesn't select rows in here,
让它,所以它不选择行,
is just- Select our table view and if you,
只是,如果你选择我们的表视图,
when you do your inspector on a table view, you'll see
当你做你的检查员表视图,您将看到
there's selection down here in the table view selector,
选择下面的表格视图选择器,
We want to change that to no selection that means
我们想要改变,这意味着没有选择
rows are not selected in our table view,
行不选择在我们的表视图,
You almost always want this in a static table view,
你总是希望在静态表视图,
Rarely are you selecting the rows in a table It it stack
很少,你选择一个表中的行它堆栈
table, sometimes you might be but rarely are you doing that,
表,有时你可能会,但很少你这样做,
And the other problem was our text field right here,
和另一个问题是我们这里的文本字段,
we wanted it to do resign first responder,
我们想做第一响应者辞职,
So I'm gonna show you a little trick here which is how we can
所以我要告诉你一个小技巧是如何
wire this text field up to our view controller as a delegate
这个文本字段连接到我们作为一个委托的视图控制器
without any code,
没有任何代码,
Okay, so do the wiring up, I'm just gonna control drag
做连接,我要控制阻力
from my text field up to my view controller,
从我的文本字段我视图控制器,
Remember this little yellow thing at the top represents
记住这个小黄色的代表
my view controller,
我的视图控制器,
So I'm gonna control drag right there and
拖在这里,所以我要控制
when I do, look, I can hook up outlets,
当我做,你看,我可以把插座,
I'm gonna hook up this text field's delegate right there,
我要把这个文本框的委托,
so now this view controller is the delegate
现在这个视图控制器是委派
of this text field,
这个文本框,
Now we still have to go back here and make it be a UI
现在我们还是要回到这里,让它成为一个UI
text field delegate and of course
文本字段代表,当然
we still want to implement our text field should return,
我们仍然希望实现我们的文本字段应该返回,
Not should clear, text field should return And
不应该清楚,文本字段应该返回和
we're just gonna have the text field resignFirstResponder,
我们要有文本字段resignFirstResponder,
Responds to [LAUGH] resignFirstResponder and
[笑]resignFirstResponder和响应
return true,
返回true,
I just want to just use that as a trick to show you you can
我只是想用这个技巧告诉你你可以
Okay, so
好的,所以
control drag to set outwards of things as well if you want,
控制拖向外设置的事情如果你想要,
So we fixed our two problems right there,
我们固定的两个问题,
So our UI should be looking good now,
所以我们的UI现在应该看上去不错,
There it is, go here,
在这里,走在这里,
Okay, let's try the text again, let's say Test, and
好的,让我们试着文本,假设测试
Return,
回报,
Design's first responder and
设计的第一反应
notice when I clicked on test it didn't click this row,
注意到当我点击测试没有点击这一行,
when I click down here, it's not clicking this row,
当我点击下面,点击这一行,
Even if I click on the edges of it
即使我点击它的边缘
Is still not selecting it,
还没有选择它,
Okay, what about the face?
好吧,面对呢?
We gotta get that face, so
我们要把那脸,所以
it's updating, based on what's going on here,
这是更新,基于这是怎么回事,
Now, we've offered the option of squinting right here, so
现在,我们已经提供的选项眯着眼,
really, what class needs to be in here?
真的,需要在这里哪个班?
What's the only class that does squinting?
什么是唯一的类,眯着眼?
It's that blinking face view controller, right?
闪烁面临视图控制器,对吧?
So we need to put an NBC in here, okay?
所以我们需要将一个美国全国广播公司(NBC)在这里,好吗?
Blinking face view controller is an NBC,
闪烁的脸视图控制器是一个美国全国广播公司(NBC),
we can't use face view, which is what I have in here now,
我们不能用脸看来,这就是我现在在这里,
Face view doesn't know how to do squinting, so
面对视图不知道如何做眯着眼,
we need to put an NBC,
我们需要将一个美国全国广播公司(NBC),
So this is where we're going to do an embedded
这是我们要做嵌入式的地方
view controller, so let's do the embedded view controller,
视图控制器,让我们来做嵌入式视图控制器,
Okay, we're gonna go here, we hit,
好的,我们会在这里,,
right now we have it's face view inside here,
现在我们这里有它的脸视图内,
So we're just gonna get rid of that face view,
所以我们要摆脱面临的观点,
we don't want that,
我们不希望这样,
Oops, I dela deleted the entire row, sorry,
哎呀,我菲律宾人质删除整行,对不起,
Is that my face view right there?
是,我的脸视图?
Yeah, so we'll delete the face view and
是的,我们会查看和删除的脸
instead of having a face view, I'm gonna go over here and
而不是一张脸看来,我要在这里
look for a container view,
寻找一个容器视图,
Container, there it is,
容器,这是,
container view, I'm gonna drag this container view in here,
容器的观点,我将这个容器视图拖到这里,
I'm gonna do the exact same thing as I did before,
我要做我之前做的一样的,
I'm gonna use my bl let's, zoom in a little so
我要用我的提单我们,放大一点
I can see it a little better,
我可以看得更清楚,
I'm gonna use my da dash blue lines to place this thing
我要用我的da冲蓝线将这个东西
where I want,
我想要的,
I'm still going to do reset to constraint, I'm going to check
我仍然要做重置为约束,我要检查
that make sure that this is all hooked up right,
确保这是所有连接正确,
It appears to be hooked up right,
它似乎是连接正确,
look what also appeared, it's kind of hidden,
看看也出现,它是隐藏的,
it's kind of afraid, there it is, right here,
有点害怕,在这里,在这里,
Okay, when we created this in it also created this
好的,当我们创建这个在它还创建了这个
new NBC right here,
新NBC在这里,
Okay, this is the MVC whose self,view is going to appear
好的,这是自我的MVC、视图将会出现
right here, and all the auto layout constraints are gonna
在这里,所有的会自动布局约束
apply to it and everything so
适用于它,所以的一切
it's gonna be fit in there and everything,
它会适应那里的一切,
So what do we want this to be?
我们希望这是什么?
Wel, we want it to be a blinking,
嗯,我们希望它是一个闪烁,
face view controller,
面视图控制器,
So I'm gonna go here, go to identity, Fir-,
所以我要去这里,去身份,冷杉,
I'm gonna select this,
我要选择这个,
Go to identity and say blinking face view controller,
去身份和说闪烁的脸视图控制器,
Of course, I have to still build the UI of this thing and
当然,我还必须构建UI的和
of course it has a face view in it,
当然它面临视图,
So I'm gonna again try and copy and paste,
所以我要再次尝试复制粘贴,
it didn't work last time I did it but we'll try again,
它没有上次我做,但我们将再试一次,
Paste, there we go,
粘贴,好了,
Okay and so we're gonna make it fit perfectly
好的,所以我们要让它完美
in here as usual, ahead and reset,
在这里像往常一样,重置,
Adjust constraints and of course, this phase view right
调整约束,当然,这一阶段的观点正确
here needs to be wired up as an outlet of this blinking
这里需要连接一个出口闪烁
face view controller and how am I gonna do that?
脸视图控制器,我要怎么做呢?
Same way I did that text field delegate, so,
同样我文本字段委托,所以,
we'll control drag now from the view controller to this
我们会控制拖现在从视图控制器
face view and wire it up,
面视图和线,
We don't have to bring up the code,
我们不需要把代码,
in a side by side window, especially this is a pain for
并排在一个窗口中,尤其是这是一个痛苦
blinking view controller,
闪烁的视图控制器,
Because, the, it's a subclass of it, a superclass,
因为,它的一个子类,一个超类,
rather that we're hooking up to, etc, okay?
而我们勾搭等等,好吗?
So I built this embedded view, I've created the MVC is
所以我建这个嵌入视图,我创建了MVC
actually the way I want and so now if we run,
其实我想现在如果我们运行,
We should have that blinking view controller embedded
我们应该有闪烁的视图控制器嵌入式
inside of this into that row and
在进这一行
of course it should be square,
当然应该是广场,
And all those things just as if it were the regular
和所有这些东西一样普通
face view I'm sure that here it is,
我相信这是面对视图,
Okay now, how do make it so
好,怎么让它如此
when we change these things, it changes this?
当我们改变这些事情,它改变了呢?
Well, this is just a segue right here, so
好吧,这只是一个segue这里,
in our prepare for segue,
在我们准备segue,
we're gonna grab onto that blinking view controller,
我们要抓住,闪烁的视图控制器,
And then every time things change, we'll just tell
然后每次变化,我们就告诉
the blinking view controller what its expression is, so
闪烁的视图控制器的表达式,所以
let's give this thing a name,
让我们给这件事一个名字,
We'll call this our EmbedFace, segue right here, and let's
我们称之为EmbedFace,继续在这里,让我们
go back to our editor and it's the thing we're segueing from,
回到我们的编辑器,它是我们segue从,
So it's the thing that gets to prepare, so let's go prepare
所以的准备,所以我们准备去吧
for segue, and inside this prepare for segue,
继续,在这个准备segue,
All we really need to do is grab onto that Face view
我们真正需要做的就是抓住那张脸视图
controller, so let's create a little private var,
控制器,所以让我们创建一个私有变量,
which we'll call our faceViewController,
我们称之为faceViewController,
It's going to be of type linkingFaceViewController and
这将是linkingFaceViewController和类型
it's not set initially, so we'll have it be an optional,
这不是最初,我们必须是一个可选的,
And here I'm just gonna say if the segue,destination
这里我只是想说如果segue,目的地
view controller is, actually we'll even say if let,
视图控制器,我们甚至会说如果,
Let's say if let Controller we didn't mean to do that,
比方说如果让控制器我们并不想这样做,
actually I can do an even easier way to do it,
其实我可以做一个更简单的办法去做,
Let's just say face view controller equals the segue's
假设视图控制器= segue的脸
destination as a blinking view controller and
目的地是一个闪烁的控制器和视图
if it's not a blinking view controller and won't work,
如果它不是一个闪烁的视图控制器和不会工作,
Then of course we probably want to check our identifier
当然,我们可能要检查我们的标识符
here so we'll say if the segue's identifier =,
所以我们会说如果segue的标识符=,
what did I call it?
我把它叫做什么?
Embed Face,
嵌入的脸,
Then we'll do this,
然后我们会做这个,
Okay? So all I did here,
好吧?
when I'm preparing, is just grab onto
当我准备的时候,只是抓住
that view controller, so now I have the view controller,
视图控制器,所以现在我有视图控制器,
So for example, when updateFace happens, okay?
举个例子,当updateFace发生,好吗?
Instead of printing out on the console,
而不是打印在控制台上,
I can just say that my faceViewController
我可以说我faceViewController
expression equals my expression, right?
=我的表情,表达对吗?
My expression is this thing right here, cool with that?
我的表达是这里,酷吗?
Let's go see that,
我们去看,
Okay, so we go here, we add eyes closed,
好的,我们去这里,我们添加闭上眼睛,
looking good and the frown there, grin,
看上去不错,皱眉,笑,
Notice that it started out with the wrong face though,
注意,它一开始错误的脸,
so probably,
所以很可能,
when I grab that face view controller right here,
当我抓住那张脸视图控制器,
probably want to update it right away with my expression,
可能想和我的表情,马上更新
Whatever expression I have now,
无论表达我现在,
In other words, as soon as that embedded segue gets
换句话说,只要嵌入segue
embedded, I wanna have it update with my my face, but
嵌入式,我想更新我的我的脸,但是
it's working, and it even works for squinting, okay?
它的工作,甚至为斜视工作,好吗?
So we got squinting even happening in here,
我们甚至有斜视发生在这里,
All right, we got this awesome system here,
好的,我们得到了这个可怕的系统,
this awesome MVC for editing and
这个可怕的编辑和MVC
emotion right with the emotion's name and its face,
情绪与情感的名字和它的脸,
So how do we communicate what we just edited back?
那么我们如何沟通我们刚才编辑吗?
And that's through unwinding ao let's go ahead and
这是通过解除ao让我们继续
create an unwind segue back to our presenter okay,
创建一个放松segue回到我们的主持人好,
And let's move this thing so we can see this whole thing,
我们把这件事我们可以看到整个事情,
what we're doing here,
我们在做什么,
So we're going to create an unwind from a done button in
所以我们要创建一个放松的完成按钮
this, and it's going to unwind back to this guy,
这个,它会放松回到这个家伙,
And when it unwinds we'll communicate the expression and
当它展开我们的表达和交流
the name of the expression that was chosen here in this
的名称被选在这个表达式
editor,
编辑器,
Now what's the first thing we want to do in unwind?
现在我们要做的第一件事是什么在放松吗?
We need to create that magic method to unwind to, that's
我们需要创建,神奇的方法放松,这是
always the first thing you're gonna do when you unwind,
总是你要做的第一件事当你放松时,
So that's over here in this EmotionsViewController, so
这就是在这EmotionsViewController,所以
let's go over to the EmotionsViewController, and
让我们去EmotionsViewController,
create that magic method, put it right here at the top,
创建这个神奇的方法,把它在顶部,
Okay, it's gotta be an IBAction,
好了,这是要IBAction,
Okay, just a function, we can call it anything we want,
好吧,只是一个函数,我们可以叫它任何我们想要的,
I'll call this,
我叫,
addEmotionalFace, because that's what it's gonna do,
addEmotionalFace,因为它会做什么,
it's gonna add an emotional face to this array right here,
它会添加一个情感面对这个数组,
And I'll say from segue
并从segue我会说
UIStoryBoardSegue, and this satisfies the second thing we
UIStoryBoardSegue,这满足了我们的第二件事
have to do which it has one and only one argument,
要做它有且只有一个参数,
And hit the storyboard segue and inside here, we will use
点击故事板segue里面,我们将使用
the segue information to get the expression that we chose,
segue信息让我们选择的表达,
So, now let's go back to our storyboard,
所以,现在让我们回到我们的故事板,
And wire up that, unwind which we do right here,
连接,放松,我们在这里,
So I'm gonna add a done button right here,
所以我要添加一个按钮,完成
Click down here, this is bar button, there it is,
点击这里,这是工具栏按钮,,
Okay, I wanted a standard one again,
好的,我想要一个标准,
this is the done button,
这是“完成”按钮,
See all these standard ones we had add for
看到所有这些标准的我们添加了
the other one, cancel for the other one, done for this one,
为另一个,另一个,取消了这一个,
So we have done and
所以我们所做的
I'm just gonna control drag, over there?
我要控制阻力,在那里?
No, up here,
不,在这里,
Okay, so this exit button,
这个退出按钮,
look what appeared there, add emotional face from,
看看出现,加上情绪的脸,
When I let go,
当我放手,
Notice that it puts the little from
注意,它把小
that was the external name on the end of it,
这是在结束时,外部的名字
It's kind of a backwards compatibility with objective c
这是一种用objective - c向后兼容性
there and so, I click that I want that connection and
所以,我希望连接和点击
now it's made that segue,
现在,segue,
Now where is that segue?
现在这个segue在哪?
If I zoom out am I gonna be able to see
如果我缩小我要能够看到
that on my storyboard?
在我的故事板吗?
No, you don't see it, so
不,你没有看到它,所以
where are things that you can't see in your storyboard?
是你看不见的东西在你的故事板吗?
Where do you go to find them?
你在哪里去找到他们吗?
Yeah, the document outline here,
是的,这里的文档大纲,
so let's go to the document outline and sure enough,
让我们去文档大纲,果然,
Look at that, unwind segue to add emotional faces,
看,unwind添加情绪面孔,
right here,
在这里,
we could give this segue,
我们可以给这个segue,
A name, maybe we could call it
一个名字,也许我们可以叫它
add emotion because that's what it does, right?
增加情感,因为这就是它的作用,对吧?
It calls this add emotional face so
它调用这个增加情感的脸
it kind of add emotion segue,
它添加情感segue,
Now we could transfer our information kind of
现在我们可以传递我们的信息
either way, either in the prepare in this guy,
无论哪种方式,在准备这个家伙,
But I usually like to do it in this guy because this is
但我通常喜欢用这个,因为这是
the guy who I would have to create some public API to add
的人我必须创建一些公共API添加
an emotional face or something,
一种情感的脸,
So I'm just gonna have this guy and his special method,
所以我要有这家伙和他的特殊方法,
He's going to ask the editor there what is your expression
他要问编辑你的表情
and name and it's gonna add it to his model here,
和名称,它会将它添加到他的模型,
All right, so we're gonna say if we can let
好吧,如果我们可以让我们会说
the editor, basically we'll call it editor,
基本上我们叫它编辑器,编辑器
If we can let the editor equal the segue is what?
如果我们可以让编辑等于segue是什么?
The source, it's the source of the segue,
源,它的来源segue,
we're segueing from the editor to this guy,
我们segue从编辑到这家伙,
So this as a ExpressionEditorViewCOntrol-
这是一个ExpressionEditorViewCOntrol -
ler, so if I'm able to get the editor,
l,所以如果我能编辑,
then I'm just gonna say EmotionalFaces,
然后我要EmotionalFaces说,
Not kGuard [LAUGH] EmotionalFaces, append, and
不是kGuard[笑]EmotionalFaces、附加和
I wanna append a tuple, and the tuple is
我想添加一个元组,而元组
gonna have the editor's name, and the editor's expression,
要编辑的名字,编辑器的表达式,
That's it!
就是这样!
To unwind?
放松吗?
Super simple, all right,
超级简单,
So, here's, we got worried,
这是,我们担心,
We got happy, we got sad,
我们有快乐,悲伤,
Let's add another one, let's go, I don't know,
加另一个,我们走吧,我不知道,
Now let's go, okay, this face looks like contentment to me,
现在我们走吧,好了,这张脸看起来对我满意,
he looks content so
他看起来内容
we're going to call this one content,
我们要调用这一内容,
Content, content, there it is, okay?
内容,内容,在这里,好吗?
So we've got this named content, eyes closed, grin,
所以我们有这个内容命名,闭着眼睛,笑容,
I'm going to hit done right here, it's going to unwind and
我要做在这里,它会放松
add that, hopefully, and it didn't show,
添加,希望,它没有显示,
Anyone have an idea why it didn't show there?
有人有一个想法,为什么它没有显示吗?
Because we appended it to our model, but
因为我们添加到我们的模型,但是
we never told the tableview to update,
我们从来没有告诉tableview更新,
Okay, so this is a common thing you'll do, you'll update
好了,这是一种常见的事情你会做,你就会更新
your model and you're like, my tableview doesn't work,
你的模型,你喜欢,我的表视图不起作用,
And we just need to do tableview here,
我们只需要做表视图,
reload data cuz it to call of
因为它叫重新加载数据
its UI table view data source methods again,
它的UI表视图数据源的方法,
Hopefully you experience that,
希望你的经验,
maybe in your homework assignment,
也许在你的作业,
You're used to this particular forgetfulness but
你习惯这个特别健忘
here we go, try again,
我们开始吧,再试一次,
Okay, we'll do content again, I liked content, content,
好的,我们也会做同样的内容,我喜欢的内容,内容,
Tent there it is and content was what did I say, green,
帐篷和内容是什么我说,绿色,
Eyes closed yes looks content, done, there's content,
闭上眼睛看起来是的内容,完成,有内容,
We click on it, we've got content,
我们点击它,我们有内容,
we've got worried, we've got happy,
我们担心,我们有快乐,
Whoops, happy, okay?
哦,快乐,好吗?
Everybody understand that unwinding?
大家都明白,解除?
Everyone understand the modal?
大家都理解模态?
Lets go take a look at this on iPad,
让我们去看看这个iPad,
lets see what it looks like here,
让我们看看它是什么样子,
Okay, let's make this a lot smaller,
好的,让我们把这个小很多,
is that the smallest we can make it?
这是最小的我们可以让它吗?
No, four, here we go,
不,四,我们开始吧,
Okay, so here it is on iPad well,
好吧,这是iPad,
lets go to landscape here, make sure it's working,
让去,确保它是工作,
Sad, happy, worried, lets add another one, woah!
悲伤,快乐,担心,允许添加另一个,哇!
Big face, now, this is the kind of UI that in your final
大脸,现在,这是你最后的UI
project you're going to get dinged on the UI
项目你会得到升到UI
part of the rubric, because this is a horrible UI,
标题的一部分,因为这是一个可怕的UI,
Look at the tiny, little things at the bottom,
看小,小事在底部,
gigantic face this is a classic,
巨大的脸这是一个经典的,
my app works on iPad and iPhone, okay?
我应用在iPad和iPhone,工作好吗?
Because I just
因为我刚
clicked the button that said do iPad, okay?
点击按钮,说做iPad,好吗?
Sometimes we have to do more to make things work on both
有时候我们必须做更多的工作
platforms and in this case, clearly this is bad UI,
平台和在这种情况下,显然这是糟糕的UI,
it's an opportunity to make points on your rubric and your
这是一个在你的标题和机会点
And in fact,
事实上,
final project by implementing an iPad specific idiom,
通过实现iPad最终项目特定的成语,
In this case that's what we wanna do this clearly wants to
在这种情况下,这就是我们想要这样做显然想
be in a pop over,
在流行,
When we click this little plus we want this a little
当我们点击这个小加上我们希望这一点
to appear right here in that little pop over, so
出现在那个小流行,所以
what do we need to do that?
我们需要做什么?
Is could be simpler, we gonna go back to our story bore here
是可以更简单,我们会回到我们的故事了吗
and we're gonna change this segue,
我们要改变这个segue,
which is currently our modal segue, right?
目前我们的模态segue,对吧?
The modal segway from emotions right here
模态赛格威的情绪
over to this editor from being modal to being a popover,
在这个编辑器从模态是一个弹出窗口,
Now we know that it automatically is going to
现在我们知道,它自动会
adapt to being like modal full screen on the iPhone,
适应,像iPhone上的模态全屏,
So by changing it to popover it's gonna work now on
因此通过改变弹窗的工作
both platforms but
两个平台,但
we're going to see a little bit of problems here,
我们将会看到一些问题,
All right, so, let's try it, plus, nice, okay,
好吧,让我们试试,另外,不错,好吧,
Maybe not seeing this very well because of the high
可能没有看到这很好,因为高
resolution being scaled way down but
向下扩展但决议
it's picked a reasonable size, it's a little bigger than
选择一个合理的大小,它是一个小比
it needs to be, it's a reasonable size,
它需要一个合理的大小,
But there's actually one thing that's wrong with this UI
但有一件事是错误的,这个UI
which is this cancel button right here,
这里的取消按钮,
Okay on in a pop over you don't have cancel buttons
好的在流行在你没有取消按钮
because watch if I click over here it canceled it, so
因为看如果我点击这里取消它,
I don't need this cancel button right here,
我不需要这个取消按钮,
I need it on iPhone but I don't need it on iPad, so
我需要它在iPhone iPad但是我不需要它
let's add a little bit of code to take this cancel
让我们添加一些代码来把这个取消
button out,
按钮,
If we're actually in a pop over,
如果我们在一个流行,
and the way I'm going to tell I'm in a pop over is I'm going
我要告诉我的方式在一个流行的是
to look at my pop over presentation controller,
看我的流行表示控制器,
And see if my arrow is pointing any way, and if my
看看我的箭头指向任何方式,如果我的
arrow is pointing somewhere I must be in a pop over,
箭头指向的地方我必须在一个流行,
If i don't have an arrow then I'm probably over full screen,
如果我没有箭那么我可能在全屏幕,
Okay so let's go ahead and do that,
好,让我们继续这样做,
Let's go back here to our editor and
让我们回到这里,和编辑
in our editor, I'm gonna do this in view will appear,
在我们的编辑,我要做这个视图将会出现,
Nice late in the game time to do it, so view will appear,
好晚的游戏时间,所以视图将会出现,
super view will appear,
父视图将显示,
I'm just gonna say in here, if I can If I can, and here I'll
在这里我只是想说,如果我可以,如果我可以,我将在这里
make it wide so that I have pick good variable names here,
让它宽,这样我有选好的变量名,
If I can let popoverPresentationController
如果我能让popoverPresentationController
= my navigationControllers popoverPresentationController,
=我的导航控制器popoverPresentationController,
Now, why am I giving that
现在,为什么我给
navigationControllers popoverPresentationController?
导航控制器popoverPresentationController吗?
Cuz it's actually the highest level MVC
因为它实际上是MVC的最高水平
that's in the popover, okay?
在弹出窗口,好吗?
Also, that cancel button
同时,取消按钮
is in the navigationController, right?
在导航控制器,对吧?
It's part of the navigation items for
这是导航项目的一部分
the navigationController,
导航控制器,
so if I'm not in a navigationController,
如果我不在导航控制器,
this whole thing is kinda useless anyway,
这整个事情是有点用处,
So here I'm gonna say if the popoverPresentationControll-
这里我想说如果popoverPresentationControll -
er's arrowDirection equals unknown, or well let's say if
er arrowDirection等于未知,或假设
it doesn't equal unknown, so it points somewhere,
它不等于未知,所以点的地方,
Then I must be in a popover, so I'm gonna remove
然后我必须在一个弹出窗口,所以我要删除
from my navigation items, my left bar button item,
从我的导航项,我的左栏按钮项目,
Okay, remember navigation item is what controls, what bar
好的,记得导航项控制什么,酒吧
buttons appear when you are in a navigation controller,
按钮出现在导航控制器,
Okay, so here we go, we click, no cancel button
好吧,我们走,我们点击,没有取消按钮
which is good and we'll run it on iPhone in a second and
这很好,我们会在iPhone上运行它第二
we'll make sure the cancel button is still there,
我们会确保取消按钮仍然存在,
Okay, what's another problem here though?
好吧,还有什么问题吗?
Well the problem is this is a little too big,
问题是这个有点太大了,
it's kind of got this extra space down here at the bottom
这是一种有底部下面这个额外的空间
that we don't want, okay?
我们不希望,好吗?
And, in fact, if I go this way, and I slide this out and
事实上,如果我走这条路,我滑出去
bring this up, now it's a little too small, so
把这个,现在有点太小了,所以
it's either a little too small or too big,
这是有点太小或太大,
That's because it doesn't know how big this thing is, so
那是因为它不知道这个东西有多大,所以
it's just picking kind of standard sizes,
它只是挑选的标准尺寸,
For these particular orientations, so
对于这些特定的方向
let's teach this MBC, this editor MBC, how big it is,
让我们教这个MBC,这个编辑MBC,它是多大,
And we're gonna do that by adding up all the heights
我们要做的,通过添加所有的高度
of all the rows and seeing which row is the widest,
的所有行,看到这行是最宽的
By doing that, we'll be able to see how big this section
通过这样做,我们就能看到本节多大
in the table view is, we'll do that, and
在表视图中,我们将这样做,和
view will appear also,
视图也会出现,
I'm gonna say here, var size = tableView,, well,
点击这里,var = tableView大小,,好吧,
it'd really be nice if I had a method called minimumSize
就真的好了如果我有一个方法叫做minimumSize
forSection: 0, okay, if it could just tell me the size,
forSection:0,如果它可以告诉我大小,
And unfortunately, tableView doesn't have a thing like that
不幸的是,tableView没有这样的事情
but luckily for you I have such a thing right here
但对你来说幸运的是我有这样一个东西
as an extension today will view and we don't have time
今天为一个扩展视图和我们没有时间
to type it all in such like quick typed it,
输入所有类似快速输入,
But you can see as pretty easy it's just goes through all
但是你可以看到很简单只是经过
the rows in the section that you ask and it gets the cell
部分的行,你问和细胞
at that row or even creates a cell at that row if necessary,
在这一行,甚至创建一个细胞在这一行如果有必要,
And then it uses this really cool method here, system
然后它使用这个很酷的方法,系统
layout, size fitting, UI layout, fitting compress size,
布局,大小合适,UI布局,装配压缩规模,
This guy right here uses auto layout
这家伙在这里使用自动布局
to say what's the smallest this thing can be, okay?
说什么最小的这个东西,好吗?
So this is a really cool little function
这是一个很酷的小功能
that you can do in UI view,
你可以在UI视图,
By the way, notice I'm sending that to the content view of
顺便说一下,请注意我发送的内容视图
each cell,
每一个细胞,
We didn't talk about content view but
但我们没有讨论内容视图
each table view cell has a content view that's where all
每个表视图单元格有一个视图的所有内容
the contents really are,
内容是什么
And that's the thing you want to ask to apply all the auto
这就是你想问的所有汽车应用
layout rules to see if it will fit,
布局规则,看看它是否适合,
So then here I'm just getting the one that's has that's
所以这里我刚刚的这是
the widest okay maxing the width and
最宽的宽度和好的尽最大努力
here I'm adding the heights of the rows okay?
这里我添加的行?
Height for row is just the height of the row by
高度行只是一行的高度
asking the delegate here,
问这里的委托,
Okay, so good, so we got the size this is the size,
好的,太好了,所以我们得到了尺寸大小,
but actually we got a little trickiness to do here because
但实际上我们因为有点棘手
we've got that square face view,
我们有那个方脸视图,
I still want it to be square even when I shrink it down,
我仍然想要平方,即使我把它缩小,
So I'm going to take the size's height and remove
所以我需要尺寸的高度和删除
the height that it got for that
的高度了
index path that the little face is at, that's row 1,
索引路径,小脸在第一行,
Section 0, so I'm gonna remove that and
段0,所以我要删除,
I'm gonna add back the width of the tableView,
我要添加视图的宽度,
Actually the width of the tableView I calculated,
实际上我计算表视图的宽度,
which is size, okay?
这是尺寸,好吗?
So I've just added it's square, so
所以我刚刚添加的广场
it's square in the new smaller size,
这是广场在新的尺寸小一点的,
Hopefully everybody understand what I did there, it looks
希望大家理解我所做的,它的样子
like I'm missing something here yes the parenthesis,
就像我在这里少了什么是的括号,
Set it as our prefered content size equals that size,
把它作为我们的优先内容大小等于那个大小,
So this prefered content size remember is the thing
记得是这优先内容大小
that tells the system this is how big this MVC
它告诉系统这是多大的MVC
should be when it's in a pop over,
应该在一个流行的时候,
So let's see if that worked, all right?
让我们看看如果工作,对吧?
So let's just slide it out here and click,
让我们滑出来,点击,
Perfect size right there, right?
完美的大小,对吗?
Let's do it in landscape, click, perfect size, okay?
让我们做景观,点击,完美的尺寸,好吗?
So that's how you get your pop overs to fit their size
这是你如何让你的流行越过适合它们的大小
exactly, you've gotta figure out what their size is,
没错,你必须找出他们的大小,
Okay, that might be a little work but
但这可能有点工作
once you figure out what their size especially using that
一旦你找出它们的大小尤其是使用
nice system fitting thing, you can do that,
好的系统配件的事情,你能做到这一点,
So last thing I wanna do is go back to iPhone and
所以我要做的就是回到iPhone和
see what damage we've over there by doing this
看看我们那边的损害
clicking this pop over business in,
点击这个流行业务,
Okay, so here's our iPhone version, so
好的,这是我们的iPhone版本,因此
still working here, plus it's still adapting,
仍然在这里工作,此外,它还适应,
It not, it didn't show it in a popover even though we changed
不,它没有显示在弹出窗口即使我们改变
this segue to be a popover on all platforms,
这个segue窗在所有平台上,
It does that adaptive behavior to make this happen, okay,
它的适应性行为来实现这一点,好吧,
it's still working fine, though,
不过,它仍然工作正常
Call this happy,
称之为幸福,
Works like a charm, let's take a look over here,
就像一个魅力,让我们来看看这里,
Okay?
好吧?
This is landscape mode on the phone, this is pretty good,
这是景观模式的电话,这是很好,
I'm sure, woah!
我敢肯定,哇!
Big forehead guy,
大额头的人,
Okay, now again you could argue
好了,现在你可能会说
well this is just the way it makes it be but this is bad,
这只是它的方式是但这是不好的,
This is bad UI, I mean really if you had an app and
这是糟糕的UI,我的意思是如果你有一个应用程序
you bought it and it did this you'd be like what the?
你买了它,它这样做你会喜欢吗?
Who wrote that?
谁写的?
Now this is a strange situation where on an iPhone I
这是一个奇怪的情况我在iPhone上
actually think this would look a ton better
实际上认为这看起来一吨更好
as a pop over, wouldn't it?
作为一种流行,不是吗?
Because the pop over is nice minimum size,
因为流行是不错的最小尺寸,
so if we had this thing where you clicked on this plus,
如果我们有这个东西,你点击这个加上,
And it made a nice little pop over here wow that'd be just
它做了一个漂亮的小流行在这里哇,会
really cool in landscape mode,
非常酷的景观模式,
So how can I make it stop adapting cuz that's, well
所以我怎么能让它停止适应因为这
the problem here is when I hit plus it's adapting to the fact
这里的问题是当我点击+适应这样的事实
that it's on a compact width,
它是在一个紧凑的宽度,
All right, and it's turning it to full screen, so
好吧,把它全屏幕,所以
I don't want that, I want it to still be pop over,
我不希望这样,我希望它仍然是流行,
So let's use those that delegate method thing
所以让我们用那些委托方法的事情
I was talking about to make it stop doing that,
我在谈论让它停止这样做,
So that delegate stuff happens in the prepare for
这代表东西的准备
this segway, that prepare happens over here in
赛格威,准备在这里发生
the emotions view controllers,
视图控制器的情感,
We already have a prepare for that,
我们已经有了准备,
just preparing a different segue,
只是准备不同segue,
it's the segue that actually shows the face,
segue实际上显示了脸,
So here I'm just gonna say else,
这里我只是想说,
because I'm not talking about that segue,
因为我并不是在谈论segue,
I'm gonna talking about a different one else if
我要谈论一个不同的人
the segues destination is the editor,
segue目的地是编辑,
expression editor, view controller, okay?
表达式编辑器视图控制器,对吧?
Then I wanna Prep my popoverPresentationController
然后我要准备我的popoverPresentationController
so I'm the delegate,
我委托,
So I'm gonna say,
所以我想说,
if I can let the popoverPresentationController,
如果我能让popoverPresentationController,
= segue, Destinations popover presentation controller,
= segue目的地弹窗显示控制器,
Remember that the presentation controller is always
记住,总是表示控制器
on the thing being presented,
件事被呈现,
it's controlling the presentation itself,
这是控制演讲本身,
Not the thing that's presenting, but
不提供的,但是
the thing presented,
的东西,
So now I'm just gonna tell this popover
现在我要告诉这个弹窗
presentation controller to set delegate to be myself, okay?
表示控制器设置委托自己,好吗?
And then of course I have to go up here and
当然,我得走了
say I'm a UI popover,
说我是UI弹出窗口,
Presentation controller delegates,
代表们表示控制器,
All the methods are optional, so
所有方法都是可选的,所以
I am nicely implementing that,
我很好地实施,
But I'm going to implement the one,
但是我要实现的,
which is this adaption, adaptive behavior thing,
这是适应,适应行为的东西,
It's called adaptive presentation style for
它被称为自适应表示风格
view controller, trait collection,
视图控制器,特征集合,
Right here,
在这里,
well maybe arguments a little easier to see,
也许参数更容易看到,
Okay, so this is the thing where it's asking the pop over
这是问的流行的东西
presentation manager,
报告经理,
hey do you wanna control the adapting behavior?
嘿你想控制适应行为?
Right, how it adapts, and I do,
它如何适应,我做,
And what is it that I wanna do?
我想做的是什么?
Well, when it's in landscape mode in iPhone,
当它在横向模式在iPhone,
I want it to be pop over,
我希望它是流行,
So basically what is the traitCollection
所以基本上traitCollection是什么
of the iPhone in landscape mode?
iPhone在横向模式?
It's vertically compact,
这是垂直紧凑,
It's the only case that's vertically compact,
这是唯一的垂直紧凑的情况下,
No other device has vertically compact,
没有其他设备垂直紧凑,
So I'm gonna, just gonna say if the traitCollection, okay,
所以我要,只是会说如果traitCollection,好吧,
cuz that's passed along to me here as an argument, if I,
因为这是我作为参数传递,如果我,
I'm gonna say if it verticalSizeClass = compact,
我想说如果它verticalSizeClass =紧凑,
then what's the adaptation mode I want?
然后适应模式我想要什么?
,none, do not adapt,
,没有,不适应,
Just be your normal pop over self,
只是你的正常的流行的自我,
However, if the traitCollection
然而,如果traitCollection
horizontalSizeClass is compact, I do want to adapt,
horizontalSizeClass紧凑,我想适应,
In fact, I wanna adapt to overFullScreen,
事实上,我想适应overFullScreen,
By the way, overFullScreen means full screen and
顺便说一下,overFullScreen全屏和手段
don't show the view controller behind it,
不显示视图控制器,
over, what you call, full screen,
结束了,你叫什么,全屏,
just ,FullScreen is go over the whole screen,
只是,全屏是整个屏幕,
But let the one that I'm on top of show through, and
但是让我上面给的,和
usually if we do that one, we blur, we put a blur background
通常如果我们这么做,我们模糊,我们放了一个模糊的背景
or something like that, you might check out UI visual
或类似的东西,你可能会查看界面视觉
effects, if you wanna do that in your final project,
效果,如果你想在期末项目,
UI visual effects great way to do a blur,
一个模糊界面视觉效果的好方法,
Otherwise I'm gonna return none,
否则我要返回,
because otherwise I'm regular width or height or something,
否则我常规的宽度或高度,
I'm on an iPad basically probably or
我在iPad上基本上可能或
maybe I'm on an iPhone 6+ or something like that,
也许我在iPhone上6 +之类的,
iPhone 7+ but I don't wanna adapt in those cases either,
iPhone 7 +但我不想适应在这种情况下,
All right, so this will control the adapted behavior,
好的,这将控制适应行为,
But one thing I have here is destination,
但有一件事我是目的地,
we don't want destination because the destination
我们不想要的目的地,因为目的地
of this segue is a UI navigation controller okay?
这个segue UI导航控制器?
We want here this destination view controller that we
我们希望这个目标视图控制器
calculated by looking inside the navigation controller, so
计算通过导航控制器内
this is destination view controller,
这是目标视图控制器,
Okay so now let's run this,
好,现在让我们运行这个,
Oops, >> No segue dot,
噢,> >点,
>> No segue dot, yeah,
> >没有segue点,是的,
Okay, there we go,
好了,好了,
So we've got our destination view controller B in this
所以我们有我们的目标视图控制器B
expression, then we're going to become the pop-over
表达式,然后我们会成为做客
presentation for those delegates,
表示为代表,
And we'll implement this adapted behavior where we
我们会实现这个调整我们的行为
don't do it, in the case where we're vertically compact,
不这样做,如果我们垂直紧凑,
So here this one, is vertically regular, so
这一个,是垂直固定,所以
it's not doing that,
不这样做,
But in here, we're vertically compact, so
但是在这里,我们垂直紧凑,所以
this shows up as a pop-over,
这表现为突然到来,
Right?
对吧?
long today,
今天,
And I will, see you Wednesday,
我将星期三见到你,
>> For more, please visit us at Stanford,edu,
> >更多内容,请访问我们的斯坦福大学edu,